<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
		<!--	created with www.mysitemapgenerator.com	-->
		<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
		<channel>
			<title>Dreamtech</title>
			<link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/</link>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra MC2180 Industrial Mobile Computer WiFi Barcode Scanner </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-mc2180-industrial-mobile-computer-wifi-barcode-scanner.html</link>
			       <description>Zebra MC2180 Industrial Mobile Computer WiFi Barcode Scanner Specification: Brand Zebra Model Zebra MC2180 Interface (Built-in) WiFi, Bluetooth Battery 2400mAh rechargeable Smart Li-Ion 1D Barcode 1D linear imager, 1D laser, 1D area imager 2D Barcode 2D area imager Dimensions 60.9 x 171.7 x 34.1mm Weight 240.7gm Color Regular Others Display: 2.8" QVGA with backlight TFT-LCD, 64K colors, Touchpanel: Resistive touch panel, Keypad: 27-key numeric; 2 programmable side buttons, Expansion Slot: User accessible Micro SDHC card slot (up to 32GB), Notification: LED and audible alert, CPU: Mar Warranty 1 year Made in/ Assemble Mexico/Singapore/China Country of Origin USA</description>
			       <g:price>51000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>MC2180</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/zebra-mc2180-01.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Bluetooth Printer Mini Thermal Printer Support Android + IOS </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/bluetooth-printer-mini-thermal-printer-support-android-ios.html</link>
			       <description>Bluetooth Printer Mini Thermal Printer Support Android + IOS Description: 1).Support print 58mm/width,40mm/dimensions thermal paper.Low operating costs (no ribbons, ink cartridges) 2).Support two in one printing with USB+Bluetooth (Standard), Compatiable with Andriod and iOS both systems 3).High-speed and clear printing.Easy installation for paper, simple operation 4).Super power lithium 1500mah electricity, standby time can reach 5-6 days.Auto sleep, auto awake, save electricity 5).Streamline outlook, Small size and portable, light weight, reliable performance, simple to connect and easy to use 6).Support multi-languages 7).Support logo print,QR code and barcode 8).Free SDK,Demo,customer support for application develop 9).It support Five POS software: Loyverse(Retail/Clothing), iREAP(Retail/Inventory), CasierStock(Shopping/Inventory Management), Kyte(Mobile Sales), Pozool(Restaurant/Coffee Shop) for android devices.For iOS system, it comes with DEMO APP for basic text printing, No APP to print invoice and receipts so far. Please confirm if it suits your demands before order.</description>
			       <g:price>4500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Bluetooth58dd</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/bluetooth_53.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>POINT OF SALE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> ECR Cash Register Machine For Restaurant Or Retail Store </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/ecr-cash-register-machine-for-restaurant-or-retail-store.html</link>
			       <description>ECR Cash Register Machine For Restaurant Or Retail Store Specification: Suitable For Restaurant,Cafe,Stores,good management for inventory and billing Power supply:DC12V 4A Monitor:10.1 inch capacitive touch screen Customer Display:10.1 inch(1024*600) screen, Customer Display use: LED 8 digital POS Software:Independent intellectual property rights of software Printer:58 thermal receipt printer (included in pos) Cash drawer size:33.5*36.8*8cm CPU:Freescale IMX6 SD ram/NANDFLASH:512MB/16GB Interface:2* RS232,2* USB,1*LAN,1*Cash drawer port 1. Commodity number: 60000 2. Dept. number: 10000 3. Clerk number: 1000 4. Cashier number: 1000 5. Taste number: 100 6. Discount type: 100 7. Payment type: 100 8. Member number: 20000 9. Table number: 2000 10. Tax number: 10 11. Receipt number: 6000 About pos software: *Use for restaurant or mini market *Free training for lifetime</description>
			       <g:price>24000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>ECR593-Cash</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/CASH_REGISTER_MACHINE_TOUCH.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>POINT OF SALE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Handheld 2D Barcode Scanner Wired scanner C-513 </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/handheld-2d-barcode-scanner-wired-barcode-scanner-c-513.html</link>
			       <description>Handheld 2D Barcode Scanner Wired scanner C-513 Main Features 1.. Work with device which has a USB interface , compatible with windows7/10, Mac ,Linux etc. 2. READS BARCODES ON VARIOUS MEDIA: Easily capture all common bar codes (1D, 2D and PDF417) on labels as well as on mobile phone displays. 3. TWO SCANNING MODE: trigger scan mode and Continuous Mode. you don’t need to press the trigger to scan 4. CMOS IMAGING SCANNING TECHNOLOGY: with advanced digital image acquisition function, it can identify screen code, incomplete code and fuzzy code etc Barcode types 1D: Codabar,Code 39,Code 32 Pharmaceutical (PARAF),Interleaved 2 of 5,NEC 2 of 5,Code 93,Straight 2 of 5 Industial,Straight 2 of 5 IATA Matrix 2 of 5 Code 11,Code 128,GS1-128,UPC-A,UPC-E,UCC Coupon Extended Code,EAN/JAN-8,EAN/JAN-13,MSI,GS1 DataBar Omnidirectional,GS1 DataBar Limited,GS1 DataBar Expanded,China Post(Hong Kong 2 of 5),Korea Post 2D: Codeblock A,Codeblock F,PDF417,Micro PDF417,GS1 Composite Codes,TLC39,QR Code,Data Matrix,MaxiCode,Aztec,HANXIN</description>
			       <g:price>3500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Dmax C-513</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/DMAX_C-513_QR.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> POSTEK TW6 300DPI Professional Industrial Label Printers </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/postek-tw6-300dpi-professional-industrial-lable-printers.html</link>
			       <description>POSTEK TW6 300DPI Professional Industrial Label barcode Printers Product description Printing MethodThermal Transfer Printing Resolution300 dpi Max Printing Speed4 ips (101.6 mm/s) Max Printing Width6.6″ (168 mm) Max Printing Length157″ (4000 mm) Memory8 MB FLASH ROM, 32 MB SDRAM RibbonWax, Wax/Resin, ResinRibbon roll: OD 3.54″ (90 mm) max., ID 1″ (25.4 mm) coreMax width: 220 mm; Max length: 600 m.Ink side: Out Media SensorReflective (Adjustable) / Transmissive(Adjustable) FontsFive built-in dot martrix ASCII fonts, Downloadable TrueType fonts Barcode Types1D Barcode: Code 39, Code 93, Code 128/subset A,B,C, Codabar, Interleave 2 of 5, UPC A/E 2and 5 add-on, EAN-13/8/128, UCC-128;2D Barcode: MaxiCode, PDF417, Datamatrix, QR Code. LCD DisplayGraphic Dot Matrix Weight 9 kgs DimensionsW 14.8''(375 mm) x D 17.1''(435 mm) x H 9.8''(250mm) * One Year Warranty.</description>
			       <g:price>180000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>POSTEK TW6</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/postek_w6.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE PRINTER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Honeywell Industrial Label Printer, Model Number: PM42 </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/honeywell-industrial-label-printer,-model-number-pm42.html</link>
			       <description>Honeywell Industrial Label Printer, Model Number: PM42 Product Specification Model Number PM42 Output Type Monochrome Paper Size Various Label Sizes Capacity (ppm) 1000 Dimensions (millimetre) 484 mm x 292 mm x 283 mm Weight (kilograms) 12.1 kg Interface Ethernet, Serial, USB, Parallel (Optional) Standard Ethernet, Serial, USB Supported Protocols TCP/IP suite (TCP, UDP, ICMP, IGMP), LPR/LPD, FTP, BOOTP, DHCP, HTTP, SNMPv1/2c/3, SNMP-MIBII suppor Fonts Monotype font engine Non-Latin fonts available through WTLE Max Printing Width 108 mm (4.25 in) Media Type Labels and tags, linerless and linered media Printing Thickness (millimetre) 2.4 to 10.4 mil (with cutter 3 to 7.6 mil) Style Roll-fed or fanfold Sensing Gap, notch, black mark, continuous Label Roll Max Diameter 213 mm (8.38 in) Label Roll Core 38 mm or 76 mm (1.5 in or 3 in) SDRAM 128MB Flash ROM 128MB Printer Command Languages IPL, DP, ZSim2 (ZPL-II), DSim (DPL), XML enabled for SAP AII and Oracle WMS Standards Supported RoHS Compliant, CB, CE (EN 60950-1, EN55022/EN55032 Class A), FCC Class A, RCM, KC, CRS, EAC, SASO, Power Consumption (watt) Standby 9W; Peak 300W Condition New Minimum Order Quantity 5 Unit Product Description The Honeywell PM42 mid-range industrial label printer is designed for maximum reliability and uptime. With a durable construction and an intuitive, user-friendly interface, it’s ideal for distribution center, warehouse, manufacturing, transportation and retail environments. Unlike competitive printers that incorporate plastic components, the PM42 printer features an all-metal, die-cast aluminum construction for enhanced durability and reliability in the harshest industrial environments. With a magnetic quick-mount printhead — designed for quick removal without tools — and an easily removable print roller — the PM42 printer minimizes downtime and reduces maintenance costs. With a full-color, graphical display including 9 user-selectable languages, the PM42 is intuitive and easy to use, reducing your workforce training and device support needs. And workers can easily manage their printing jobs from nearby or afar with the printer’s integrated web interface, which enables easy setup, monitoring and configuration through mobile devices including tablets and smartphones. The PM42 printer provides fast, high-volume industrial thermal printing, making it an affordable choice for organizations printing 5,000—15,000 labels per day. With its class-leading print speeds up to 300 mm/s (12 ips), you’ll gain a clear productivity advantage. And with its Smart Printing technology — delivered through Honeywell C# for Printers and Fingerprint — you can run apps, print labels and even control other devices directly from the printer, without the need for a connected PC. The user-selectable, all-in-one programming language included in every PM42 printer enables it to fit easily into most IT infrastructures, deploying quickly into existing Honeywell or mixed printer environments.</description>
			       <g:price>110000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>PM42</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/honeywell-pm42-magazzino-.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE PRINTER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> GP-L80250II 250mm/s high speed printing 3-in-1 Lan </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/gp-l80250ii-250mm-s-high-speed-printing-3-in-1-lan.html</link>
			       <description>250mm/s high speed printing GP-L80250II 250mm/s high speed printing 3-in-1 Lan Description : New flat knife structure, longer lifetime,higher stability</description>
			       <g:price>8500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>GP-L80250II</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/GP-L80250II-3-in-1-Serial-USB-Ethernet-Interface.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>POINT OF SALE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Label Printer GP-3120TU Thermal Bar code Printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/label-printer-gp-3120tu-thermal-bar-code-printer.html</link>
			       <description>Gprinter GP3120tu Thermal Barcode Printer Low Price printing cost Model: GP3120TU Printing method: Thermal Resolution: 203DPI Paper width: 25-82mm Printing speed: 2-5inch/s Reservoir:DRAM: 2M FLASH: 2M Test printer head temperature:Touch the switch slightly Explore paper: Photo sensor Interface: USB External roll diameter: Max: 115mm Inner roll diameter: Min: 25mm paper type: tear off and peel off Barcode: CODE128,EAN128,ITF,CODE39,EAN13,EAN13+2,EAN13+5,EAN8,EAN8+2,EAN8+5,CODABAR,POSTNET,UPC-A,UPCA+2,UPCA+5,UPC-E,UPCE+2,UPC-E+5,CPOST,MSI,MSIC,PLESSEY,ITF14,EAN14 Barcode setting Single character:FONT 0 to FONT 8 Extension and rotation character the character can be extended 1-10 double in crossing and portrait, printing rotation(0 ,90 ,270 , 360 ) Graph image file as PCX and BMP can be downloaded to FLASH and DRAM Fashion modeling The best Top of the material Sharp knife USB interface Durable print head Cover open button Power button Clearly labeled Detailed parameters Non-slip base Usage: 1. Open the lid 2. Place a roll of paper placed in the specified location 3. move the paddle Move to the the left, fixed 4. Pull out A small piece of label paper , Card slot Move to the left Carry out start printing support A variety of print formats You can edit directly with WORD Or a variety templates LOGO and fonts *One year Warranty.</description>
			       <g:price>7500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>GP-3120TU</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/50x25T_MM_Silver_Barcode_Label-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE PRINTER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> MX-5500 Handheld Price Labeling Gun 8 Digits </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/mx-5500-handheld-price-labeling-gun-8-digits.html</link>
			       <description>Buy Directly from Dream Tech Suppliers:MX-5500 Handheld Price Labelling Gun Plastic 8 Digits EOS Price Tag Labels Machine for Supermarket.</description>
			       <g:price>3500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>MX-5500</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/hand-labeling-machine-.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE PRINTER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> New Handheld Wired CCD Barcode Scanner Dmax x718 </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/new-handheld-wired-ccd-barcode-scanner-dmax-x718.html</link>
			       <description>New Handheld Wired CCD Barcode Scanner Dmax x718 Technical Parameters Product Specification 1D Wired CCD Barcode Scanner CPU ARM 32-bit Cortex Optical Source 620nm Visible red light diode Resolution Ratio 1500 pixel Imaging Sensor CCD Trigger Mode continuous scanning/manual trigger Indication Buzzer &amp; LED width of scan 5-30cm depth of scan 2-50cm Decoding Speed 200 times/second Interface USB ,RS232 Resolution 4mil Decoding Capability Code128,EAN-13,EAN-8,Code39,UPC-A,UPC-E, Codabar, Interleaved 2 of 5,ISBN, Code 93, UCC/EAN-128, GS1 Databar etc Max.Power 700mw Working Voltage DC5V Storage Temperature -40 C ~ 60 C Working Temperature 0 C ~ 50 C Relative Humidity 0 ~ 95% Drop test 2.0m fall to concrete Certificate CE,FCC,RoHS,IP54</description>
			       <g:price>2200 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Dmax_x718</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/DMAX_x718_d.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Honeywell Voyager 9520 General Duty Scanners </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/honeywell-voyager-9520-general-duty-scanners.html</link>
			       <description>Honeywell Voyager 9520 General Duty Scanners Description : Honeywell Voyager 9520 General Duty Scanners MECHANICAL Dimensions (LxWxH)-198 mm x 78 mm x 56 mm (7.8 in x 3.1 in x 2.2 in) Weight-149 g (5.3 oz) ELECTRICAL Input Voltage-5 VDC + 0.25 V Operating Power-600 mW (120 mA @ 5 V) Standby Power-0.45 W (90mA @ 5 VDC) Host System Interfaces-USB, RS232, Keyboard Wedge, IBM 46xx (RS485), OCIA, Laser Emulation, Light Pen Wand Emulation SCAN PERFORMANCE Scan Pattern-Single scan line Scan Speed-72 scan lines per second Scan Angle-Horizontal: 50 Symbol Contrast-35% minimum reflectance difference Pitch, Skew-68 , 52 Decode Capability-Reads standard 1D and GS1 DataBar symbologies ENVIRONMENTAL Operating Temperature-0 C to 40 C (32 F to 104 F) Storage Temperature -40 C to 60 C (-40 F to 140 F) Humidity-5% to 95% relative humidity, non-condensing 02 Years Warranty</description>
			       <g:price>10200 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Voyager 9520</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/Honeywell_Voyager_9520_colo.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra LS1203 GENERAL PURPOSE BARCODE SCANNER </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-ls1203-general-purpose-barcode-scanner.html</link>
			       <description>Zebra LS1203 GENERAL PURPOSE BARCODE SCANNER Description : Zebra LS1203 GENERAL PURPOSE BAR CODE SCANNER LS1203 handheld scanner handles all 1D bar codes and is ideal for small retailers. It delivers the functionality, features and reliability needed to improve operational efficiencies from the check-out line to the storeroom</description>
			       <g:price>4300 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>LS1203</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/zebra_ls1203_imeg.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Dmax-410 retail supermarket POS cash drawer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/dmax-410-retail-supermarket-pos-cash-drawer.html</link>
			       <description>1 MP Fixed Indoor Turret Camera Specification: MODEL NUMBER KER-410 PHYSICAL Dimension 410(W)x420(D)x100(H) mm Construction Thick gauge cold rolled steel and SECC Finish Textured hybrid powder coat Color Black, beige and custom type Roller Polyurethane for smooth operation CASH TRAY (INSERT) Construction Shatter-resistant BAS plastic Currency layout 4,5-bill with metal wire grips, 8 adjustable coin slots Media slots 1 or 2 OPERATION Drawer lock 3-positioin lock/4-functions locked open/closed, manual open, electronically driven Interface RJ11,RJ12,USB,RS232,DCΦ2.5/3.5Jack,custom type Lifecycle MTBF1,000,000 times+ Micro switch Cash drawer status micro switch</description>
			       <g:price>4800 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Dmax-410</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/DMax_DM-C8500_Electronic_Cash_Drawer-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>POINT OF SALE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> GP-5890XIII 58mm thermal receipt printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/gp-5890xiii-58mm-thermal-receipt-printer.html</link>
			       <description>Cheaper Pos Printer GP-5890XIII 58mm thermal receipt printer Specification : Print width 48mm Dot density 384dot/line Print speed 90mm/s Interface USB/ Serial/ Parallel/ Ethernet/ USB+Wi-Fi/ USB+Bluetooth Paper Width 57.5 0.5mm Paper diameter Φ83mm Line space 3.75mm can be adjustive) Column number Font A-32columns/Font B-43columns/Simplified、Traditional Chinese-16columns Character Size ANK character Font A 1.5×3.0mm 12×24dots Code page Font B 1.1×2.1mm 9×17dots Simplified/Traditional Chinese 3.0×3.0mm(24×24dots PC437/Katakana/PC850/PC860/PC863/PC865/West Europe/Greek/Hebrew/East Europe/Iran/WPC1252/PC866/PC852/PC858/IranII/Latvian/ Arabic/PT151,1251/PC737/WPC/1257/Thai Vietnam/PC864/PC1001/(Latvian)/(PC1001)/(PT151,1251)/ (WPC1257)/(PC864)/(Vietnam)/(Thai) Barcode UPC-A/UPC-E/JAN13(EAN13)/JAN8(EAN8)CODE39/ITF/CODABAR/CODE93/CODE128 Fonts GB2312 Data 4K bytes NV Flash 60K bytes Cashdrawer out DC 12V/1A Power adaptor Input AC 100V/220V,50~60Hz Output DC 12V/3A Power supply DC 12V/2.5A Weight 0.92kg Dimension 222×140×120mm L×W×H Work environment Temperature: 0~45 Humidity:10-80% Storage environment Temperature: -10~60 Humidity:10~90% Mechanism 50km</description>
			       <g:price>3500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>GP-5890XIII</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/gp_58mm_printer.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>POINT OF SALE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra GT800 203dpi Thermal Barcode Printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-gt800-203dpi-thermal-barcode-printer.html</link>
			       <description>Zebra GT800 Desktop Direct Thermal/Thermal Transfer Label Printer 203dpi Thermal Bar code Printer Zebra GT800 Desktop Label Printer GT800 direct thermal /thermal transfer printing desktop barcode printer to ensure consumers can enjoy the brilliant performance and excellent durability with favorable price, it can meet all lower grade printing applications demands offering a series of top-grade functions. With ribbon length 300m can reduce the frequency every time need to change the ribbon halting time, of 5 inches/sec printing speed, and stronger CPU processor of 32 bytes. support more pictures and much longer labels printing, which can largely improve your efficiency.</description>
			       <g:price>20500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Zebra GT800</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/Zebra_GT820_Barcode_Label_Printer_wwwdreamtechcombd-min-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE PRINTER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Laser Scan 2D Barcode Scanner Dmax- S516 </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/laser-scan-2d-barcode-scanner-dmax-s516.html</link>
			       <description>Laser Scan Bar Code Reader Corded Handheld 2D Barcode Scanner Specification: Performance Image Sensor CMOS Resoluing 640* 480 Interface USB,USB KEYBOARD,TTL232,RS232,USB COM Symbologies 2D PDF417, QR Code(Model 1/2), DataMatrix (ECC200, ECC000, 050, 080,100,140), Aztec, Maxicode, etc. 1D Code128, EAN-13, EAN-8, Code39, UPC-A, UPC-E, Codabar, Interleaved 2 of 5, ISBN, Code 93, GS1 Databar, Code 11,etc Precision: 5mil Light Source LED (630 nm 10 nm) Light Intensity 300 LUX (130 mm ) Depth of Scan Field 45 mm ~ 450 mm Print Contrast Signal 30% Roll 360 Yaw(Skew) 45 Pitch 45 Illumination 0 ~ 100,000 LUX Mechanical/ Electrical Power Consumption 1.65W Voltage DC 5 V Current : Max 450 mA Oper. 400 mA Idle 200 mA Weight 235g Size: 156*68*83 mm</description>
			       <g:price>2500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>D-S516</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/2D_CMOS_s516.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Dahua RLS1000 15kg Label Printing Scale </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/dahua-rls1000-15kg-label-printing-scale.html</link>
			       <description>Dahua RLS1000 15kg Label Printing Scale Best Quality Description : 1.Label and receipt printing , Dahua RLS1000 15kg Label Printing Scale</description>
			       <g:price>32000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>RLS1000</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/digital-barcode-weighing-scales-with-rs232-and_1-min.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE PRINTER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> ZEBRA ZT410 SERIES INDUSTRIAL PRINTERS </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-zt410-series-industrial-printers.html</link>
			       <description>ZEBRA ZT410 SERIES INDUSTRIAL PRINTERS A NEW LEVEL OF PERFORMANCE, VERSATILITY AND EASE OF USE Keep your critical operations running efficiently with Zebra’s durable ZT400 Series printers. The ZT400 offers advanced technology that drives versatility, ease of use and performance to a new level. Available in three print resolutions and two print widths, the ZT400 Series addresses a broad array of applications throughout manufacturing, transportation and logistics, retail and more. See printer status at a glance and manage settings quickly using the large color touch display. Field-installable connectivity, media handling and RFID options let you easily add new features as your needs evolve. And your IT department will find ZT400 printers easy to integrate and manage, thanks to Zebra’s Print DNA suite of applications, utilities and developer tools—all powered by Link-OS . The result? The ZT400 offers the versatility, reliability and performance to meet your industrial printing needs — today and tomorrow. Dual USB Host ports for added flexibility</description>
			       <g:price>105000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>ZEBRA ZT410</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/zebra_zt_410__barcode_printer.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE PRINTER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> DMAX S-8818 2D Table Barcode Reader </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/dmax-s-8818-2d-table-barcode-reader.html</link>
			       <description>High Quality Laser Desktop 2D Barcode Scanner Omni directional Bar code Reader for Supermarket Specification : DMAX S-8818 2D Table Barcode Reader Body Weight 150g Cable Weight 200g Cable Length 2m Dimension 105 x155 x115 (mm) (L * w * h) Light Source Visible Red light 630nm+10nm Motion Tolerance Up to 10 in./25cm per second Resolution 640(Horizontal) x 480(Vertical pixels), 256 gray levels. Interface USB,RS232 Supply Voltage DC+5V 5% Operating Temp. -20 C ~ 60 C (-4 F ~ 144 F) Storage Temp. -30 C ~ 70 C (-22 F ~ 158 F) Relative Humidity 5% ~ 95% (Non-condensing) Drop Design to withstand 0.5m drops to concrete on each of the faces Readable Symbologies 1D:UPC/EAN and with supplemental, Code 39, Code 39 Full ASCII, Tri-optic Code 39, RSS variants, UCC/EAN 128, Code 128, Code 128 Full ASCII, Code 93, Codabar (NW1), Interleaved 2 of 5, Discrete 2 of 5, MSI, Codell, IATA, Bookland EAN, Code 32, PDF417 (and Variants): PDF417, microPDF417 and composite codes, Postal: PRC, U.K., Japan, Australian, Dutch and U.S. Postnet and Planet. 2D:MaxiCode, DataMatrix(ECC 200), QR Code</description>
			       <g:price>12500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>S-8818</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/dmax_8818s.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra ZT230 Barcode Printer 203 dpi </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-zt230-barcode-printer-203-dpi.html</link>
			       <description>Feature ZT230 203 DPI definition. (8 dots/ mm) 2. Printing speed higher to 6 inches = 152mm / sec. 3. Metal frame material industrial barcode printer suits for Factory long time working. 4. Support both direct thermal printing and thermal transfer printing 5. Followed up the Stripe and S4M Traditional advantages, relax and easy operation, maintain and protection. 6. 128RAM. Printer model Zebra ZT230 Standard features Structure: metal shelf Frame with transparent window and media folded door side type consumable installation, make it easily for installation of ribbon and labels With Element Energy Equalizer (E3) Technology to make sure excellent printing quality. double color LED, quickly to monitor the printing status of the printer Multi languages and graphics user interface and full-function keyboard ( ZT230) USD 2.0 and RS-232 Serial interface comply with Energy Star Printing method Thermal sensitive / thermal transfer printing Printing definition 203dpi RAM 128 MB Printing width The narrowest width: 0.75 inches/ 19.4mm The widest width: 4.09 inches/ 104mm Printing speed 6 inches/ sec = 152mm/ sec Media sensor Transmission line, reflective Media characteristic The biggest size/ backing paper: 4.5 inches/ 114mm uncontinuous label length: 39 inches/ 991mm Media width 0.75 inches/ 19.4mm to 4.5 inches/ 114mm Printing length 203dpi: 157 inches/ 3988 MM Label diameter Outer diameter 8 inches (203dpi): core inner diameter 3 inches/ 76mm outer diameter: 6 inches (300dpi): core inner diameter 1 inch/ 25.4mm Media thickness 0.003 inch/ 0.076mm to 0.010 inch/ 0.25mm Media type continuous label, die-cutting label, black line labels , perforated label sticker Ribbon specifications: Only support thermal transfer ribbon Diameter 3.2 inches/ 81.3mm, core 1 inch/ 25.4mm Standard length 300m / 984 feet or 450m / 1476 feet ( ZT230) Proportion label with ribbon zt230 : label roll to Ribbon: 3:1 Label width 1.57 inches/ 40mm to 4.33 inches / 110mm Ribbon rewinding outside inking Environment pharameters working temperature: 40 F/ 5C to 105 F/ 40C ( thermal transfer) 32 F/ 0 C to 105 F/ 40C ( direct thermal) storage, transportion environment: -40 F/ -40C to 140F / 60C working humidity: 20% to 85% ( uncondensed) storage humidity: 5% to 85% ( uncondensed) Electric pharameters General automatic range power supply ( comply to PFC regulation) 100-240VAC, 47-63HZ Accordance with Energy Star Organization standard IEC 60950-1, EN 55022 Class B, EN 55024, EN61000 -3-2 , EN61000-3-3 cTUVus, CEMarking, FCC-B, ICES-003 , VCCk C-Tick, NOM, S-Mark, CCC , GOSTR, KCC, BSMI, UkrSepro ( ZT230) Physic pharameters Closing condition: 9.5 inches ( L) * 10.9 inches ( w) * 17 inches ( H) 242mm* 277mm * 432MM Weight: 20 pounds 9.1KG Alternative options ZebraNel a/b/g/n wireless printer server zebraNet 10/100 wiresss printer server ( insert or outputting) Centronics parallel ports ( insert) Firmware ZPLP Zebra Global printing solutions EPL2 Web View and warning ZBI 2.0 ( alternative) Barcode type One dimension: Code 11, Code 39, Code 93, with A/B/C subset Code 128 and UCC Case Codes, ISBT -128, UPC-A, UPC-E, EAN-8, EAN-13, UPC and EAN 2 Bytes or 5 Bytes expand, Plessey Postnet, Standard 2-of-5, Industrial 2-of -5, Interleave 2 of-5, Logmans, MSI, Codabar, Planet Code Two dimension codes: Aztec, Codablock, PDF 417, Code 49, DataMatrix, MaxiCode, QR Code, MicroRDF 417, TLC 39, RSS-14 Font and Graphics 7 ways dot matrix , one way smooth vector font Triumvirate TM bold compressed words ( include Agfa Mototype, Corporation UFST) Supply flexible font comply with Unicode for EMEA character set support Character set IBM Code Page 850 Support User OEM graphics and font , logo etc ZPLII draw order include the square and line</description>
			       <g:price>72000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>878</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/zt230_dd3.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE PRINTER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>S</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> DMAX S-101 Table 1D Bar code Reader </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/dmax-s-101-table-1d-bar-code-reader.html</link>
			       <description>1D Omnidirectional Laser barcode- Scanner omnidirectional Description:</description>
			       <g:price>10000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>S-101</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/DMAX_S-101_Table_12.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Bluetooth Mobile POS Printer 58 mm </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/bluetooth-mobile-pos-printer-58-mm.html</link>
			       <description>58mm Portable Mobile Printer Wireless Bluetooth Printer Mini Thermal Printer Support Android + IOS Main Features: 1).Support print 58mm/width,40mm/dimensions thermal paper.Low operating costs (no ribbons, ink cartridges) 2).Support two in one printing with USB+Bluetooth (Standard), Compatiable with Andriod and iOS both systems 3).High-speed and clear printing.Easy installation for paper, simple operation 4).Super power lithium 1500mah electricity, standby time can reach 5-6 days.Auto sleep, auto awake, save electricity 5).Streamline outlook, Small size and portable, light weight, reliable performance, simple to connect and easy to use 6).Support multi-languages 7).Support logo print,QR code and barcode 8).Free SDK,Demo,customer support for application develop 9).It support Five POS software: Loyverse(Retail/Clothing), iREAP(Retail/Inventory), CasierStock(Shopping/Inventory Management), Kyte(Mobile Sales), Pozool(Restaurant/Coffee Shop) for android devices.For iOS system, it comes with DEMO APP for basic text printing, No APP to print invoice and receipts so far. Please confirm if it suits your demands before order. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jWEEEsiHp8s&amp;t=2s</description>
			       <g:price>3600 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Blue 58</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/bluetooth_mobile_printer.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>POINT OF SALE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra GT820 Barcode Label Printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-gt820-barcode-label-printer.html</link>
			       <description>Zebra GT820 Barcode Label Printer semi Industrial Printer Specification: GT820 Thermal transfer printer / Bar code printer Model GT820 Printing method Thermal transfer printing/ direct thermal / thermal sensitive Printing resolution 8 dots / mm (203dpi/300dpi) printing speed: 127mm/ sec 5 inches Printing width: 104mm/sec 4.09" Printing length: 990 mm (39") Standard features:   300m standard ribbon   32 bytes RISC processor   In-built EPL and ZPL programmed language   3 kinds interface: serial, USB and parallel   printing method: thermal transfer and direct thermal   Housing shell double enhanced plastic structure   With Open ACCESS tm design, quickly for label media and ribbon loading.   recognized Microsoft and Windows driver programmed * ONE YEAR WARRANTY.</description>
			       <g:price>27000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>50607</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/ffpng.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE PRINTER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> DMAX C512 2D Barcode Scanner New </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/dmax-c512-2d-barcode-scanner-new.html</link>
			       <description>DMAX C512 2D Barcode Scanner New Arrival Description : Plug &amp; Play design, No need driver</description>
			       <g:price>3400 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>C512</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/DMAX_C-512_RE.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Honeywell PC42T Barcode Printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/honeywell-pc42t-barcode-printer.html</link>
			       <description>honeywell pc42t label printer Description : The PC42t is an economical solution for light-duty thermal printing applications. It's Economical to purchase and use, Honeywell pc42t bar code desktop printer. the PC42t is also a great choice for those looking to deploy thermal label printing for the first time,</description>
			       <g:price>16000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>pc42t</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/Honeywell_PC42T_Barcode_Printer__wwwdreamtechcombd-min-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE PRINTER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Restaurant Software And Hardware Package </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/restaurant-software-and-hardware-package.html</link>
			       <description>Restaurant Software And Hardware Package (Pos Printer + Software) 58mm POS Printer</description>
			       <g:price>13000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Package01</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/xp_58ii.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>SOFTWARE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Super Shop Software And Hardware Package </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/super-shop-software-and-hardware-package.html</link>
			       <description>Super Shop Software And Hardware Package (80mm Pos printer + Software) Pos Printer Rongta -325 u</description>
			       <g:price>16000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Package02</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/Rongta_RP-325.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>SOFTWARE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> RF Anti-theft antenna gate security system </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/rf-anti-theft-antenna-gate-security-system.html</link>
			       <description>Specifications Product name RF Alloy Multi- guard Brand Enguard Frequency 8.2mhz Material Aluminium alloy Dimension 157x37x10 cm Main board Dual board(3800 or other types for your choice) Imput voltage DC24V Function Install on retail store to anti theft Applicable scope Supermarket, clothing store, cosmetic store, bookshop, retail store Certification CE, ROHS, ISO9001 Warranty 1 year OEM &amp; ODM support</description>
			       <g:price>76000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>RF-10</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/EAS_System_Antenna_SSLT-RF_S5588-min_1.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>EAS SOLUTION</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> EAS am clothing Security anti-theft pencil Tag </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/eas-am-clothing-security-anti-theft-pencil-tag.html</link>
			       <description>EAS am clothing Security anti-theft pencil plastic Tag DT-002 EAS Mini Pencil Tag Brand Dmax Color black/white/grey/customized Frequency 58KHz Material ABS Lock magnetic locking Dimension 46*19*13mm Packing 1000pcs/ctn, 6.5kg/ctn MOQ 1pc Sample free</description>
			       <g:price>15 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>pencil Tag</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/hard_tag_2.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>EAS SOLUTION</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> EAS Label System Management Software </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/eas-label-system-management-software.html</link>
			       <description>EAS Label System Management Software A Comparative Study of Electronic Article Surveillance (EAS) System Let's imagine for the moment that you own a large department store, and you are having a big problem with shoplifting .What are you going to do? EAS systems and sensors gate You cannot let it continue, because every month your accounting system tells you that you are losing thousands of dollars to theft. It forces you to raise your prices, and that means you have to charge more than the store next door. That can make it very hard to compete, especially if the store next door is successfully discouraging shoplifting. As a retailer focusing on the problem of what's known in the industry as loss prevention, you basically have three methods at your disposal to slow the shoplifters down You can watch everyone in the store like a hawk and make sure they don't steal anything. You can make things hard to remove from the store by bolting them down, attaching cables, putting things in display cases and behind the counter You can use a system that attaches special tags onto everything so that an alarm goes off whenever a shoplifter tries to walk out with an item.anti thrift system Here for the purpose of security the EAS(Electronic Article Survelliance)systems are discussed and finally comparisons are made. What we do Anti thrift system Checkpoint Systems is the only vertically integrated solution provider for retail. With consumer demands accelerating at an extraordinary rate driven by technology, Checkpoint delivers intelligent solutions — bringing clarity and efficiency into the retail environment anytime, anywhere. Through a unique offering of software, hardware, labels, tags and connected cloud based solutions, Checkpoint optimizes retail operations and efficiencies with real-time intuitive data delivered throughout the supply chain and in-store resulting in improved profitability and an enriched consumer experience.</description>
			       <g:price>79000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>EAS-TOWER</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/EAS_System_Antenna_SSLT-RF_S5588-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>EAS SOLUTION</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Android Smart POS With Printer TAP02 </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/android-smart-pos-with-printer-tap02.html</link>
			       <description>TAP02 can use for store owner or system integrate company use SDK develop new app . Tenkoto come out new app which can manage membership payment can support scan Barcode or use client ID manager cash register system. Android smart POS, operating system Android 6.0, full touch screen, 5.0-inch large screen, long standby, with 3.75V low-power printer, longer endurancethermal paper printing, camera 500W pixels. GSM 2G/3G, WIFI, Bluetooth, GPS, top quality, expanding market choice, applicable to supermarket chains, chain restaurants, convenience stores, clothing stores, bakery shops Such cashiers, payments, invoicing and business management functions.</description>
			       <g:price>14000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>AP02</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/android_terminal.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>POINT OF SALE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> GPrinter Pro5 Two Color Dot matrix Printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/gprinter-pro5-two-color-dot-matrix-printer.html</link>
			       <description>Pro5 Two Color Dot matrix Printer use Ribbon Description: Two-color printing function Dot matrix Printer. 5 line/sec High-Speed Printing Support multiple international languages Support receipt reminder function Compatible with EPSON ESC/POS command sets Support automatic alarm when the printer out of pape,overheating and printing head error Build-in black mark sensor, Support black mark detection positioning pringting Support Ethernet printing Support parallel port, serial port, USB port, Ethernet port,Bluetooth Ethernet printer can achieve 2 connected tasks at the same time saved Support advanced OPOS applications Support for printing different density bitmap and download graphics Printer status monitoring</description>
			       <g:price>17000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>PRO-5</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/GPrinter_Pro5_Two_Color_Dot_matrix_Printer_wwwdreamtechcombd-min-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>POINT OF SALE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Rongta RP-58 Thermal Receipt Printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/rongta-rp-58-thermal-receipt-printer.html</link>
			       <description>Rongta RP-58 mm 2 inch Thermal Receipt Printer Big gear,Long-life,High speed,Durable Low noise direct thermal printing 3. Exquisite design and easy to use 4. Function setup, auto-printing prompt 5. Easy paper loading design, widely used in various industries Printing Method Direct Thermal Printing Paper out detection Support Paper Loading Easy Paper Width 58mm Effective Printing Width 48mm Printing Speed Max. 100mm/s Resolution 8 dots/mm(384 dots/line) Print Head Life  100km Printing length Barcode type 125, UPC-A, UPC-E, EAN-8, EAN-13, Codebar, Code39, Code93, Code128, Code11, MSI Character 6x8dots, 8x16dots, or 12x24dots Character Set GB2312, 16x16dots, or 24x24dots Power Supply 9V, 3A Cash box control 12V, Paper Thermal paper( 57mm wide, 50mm) Interface USB, Serial, Parallel, Input Power DC 3.5 ~ 9V/DC 5V, 15W Operation Temperature 5 C~50 C Humidity 10%~80% Storage Temperature -40 C~60 C Humidity 10%~90% Dimension 210mm(L)x135mm(W)x130mm(H) Weight 1kg ONE YEARS WARRANTY.</description>
			       <g:price>2800 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>2333</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/DS-2CE16D0T-IT5F-36im_wwwdreamtechcombd-min-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>POINT OF SALE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> XP-P800 Bluetooth Mobile Printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/xp-p800-bluetooth-mobile-printer.html</link>
			       <description>XP-P800 Bluetooth Mobile Printer 80 mm Print size Specification Printing method Direct thermal Printer Resolution 203 dpi Printing speed 50mm/s Paper width 80mm Paper thickness 0.06-0.08mm Paper roll diameter 40mm Interface USB+ Serial+ Bluetooth Print command Compatible with ESC/POS Printing head life 50km Input buffer 32K Bytes</description>
			       <g:price>8000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>XP-800</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/XP-P800_Bluetooth_Mobile_Printer-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>POINT OF SALE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> XP-58III Thermal POS Printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/xp-58iii-thermal-pos-printer.html</link>
			       <description>XPrinter XP-58III 58 mm/2 inch Thermal POS Printer Specification: Printing method Direct thermal Print font FONT A: 33 or 35 FONT B: 40 or 42 Character size Font A : 12 × 24 Font B : 9 × 17 Chinese: 24 X 24 Barcode JAN13(EAN13) JAN8(EAN8) CODE39 Printing command compatible with EPSON ESC/POS Language Buyer language support Character per line 384dots/line Printing speed 90mm/sec Paper width 57.5 0.5mm Paper thickness 0.06-0.08mm MCBF (life) 50mm Dimension 215×135×107mm Gross weight 0.82 KG Auto cutter No Sensor Paper Near End Sensor, Paper End Sensor, Cover open sensor Roll paper φ65mm Driver Win 9X/Win ME/Win 2000/Win 2003/Win NT/Win XP/Win Vista/win 7 Power supply DC12V/2.6A Interface Parallel USB</description>
			       <g:price>3200 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>87576</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/DS-2CE16C0T-IRP_dreamtechcombd-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>POINT OF SALE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra Gk888t Label Sticker Printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-gk888t-label-sticker-printer.html</link>
			       <description>GK888T Desktop thermal transfer zebra barcode label printer Specifications 1.zebra barcode label printer 2.thermal transfer or direct thermal 3.small footprint and low profile 4.RS-232/USB interface Zebra GK888t thermal transfer desktop printer can provide excellent performance and reliability, applicable to all kinds of middle and low quantity print application. Space-saving design, 32-bit processor, print quickly, also have large capacity memory, can realize more pictures storage, longer tag format and faster processing. This type of equipment also support EPL and strong ZPL programming language. GK888t can easily integrated into all kinds of printing applications, including government departments - asset management, document management, evidence tracking; Health care - laboratory sample and blood bank tags; Retail - price tag and receipt print; Manufacturing, light industry, products and freight tags; Transportation and logistics, boarding pass, parking card. GK888t with serial, parallel and USB interface, can meet different connection needs. Main Specification Product Type Desktop printer Resolution 203dpi (8dot/mm) Print Method Thermal Transfer / Direct Thermal Print Speed 4 IPS (102mm/s) Print Width 104mm Print Length 991mm 1D Code 11 Code 39 Code 93 Code 128 UPC-A UPC-E EAN-8 EAN-13 EAN-14 UPC-A UPC-E EAN 2 or 5 digit extensions Plessey POSTNET Standard 2 of 5 Industrial 2 of 5 Interleaved 2 of 5 LOGMARS MSI Codabar GS1 DataBar (formerly RSS) 2D Aztec Codablock Code 49 Data Matrix MacroPDF417 MaxiCode MicroPDF417 PDF417 QR Code Interface USB RS-232 Parallel Ethernet (Optional) Memory 8MB FLASH memory, 8MB SDRAM Sensor Reflective, Transmission Media Media Type Reel or folding paper, label paper, tag materials, receipt paper and wrist strap. Media Length 991mm Media Width 108mm Thickness 0.003-0.007’’ (0.08-0.18mm) Max Diameter 5’’ (127mm) Core Diameter 1.0-1.5’’ (25.4-38mm) Ribbon Ribbon Length 244’’ (74M) Ribbon Width 1.33-4.3’’ (33.8-110mm) Ribbon Ratio 1:1 Ribbon OD 1.34’’ (34mm) Core ID 0.5’’ (12.7mm) Parameter Dimension (L*W*H) 201x173x56mm Net Weight 1.5kg Power Supply AC 100-240V, 50/60Hz</description>
			       <g:price>16000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Gk888t</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/Promotion-zebra-barcode-printer-GK888T-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE PRINTER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>74M</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> GP3120TUB Thermal Barcode Printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/gp3120tub-thermal-barcode-printer.html</link>
			       <description>GP3120TUB Thermal Printer Simple and easy to install paper, thermal printer, no need carbon belt. Give barcode editing software (online transfer, provide video tutorials), compatible with the computer system of Window 7 / 8.1. clothing label printer, label barcode printer, barcode printer, Cheap clothing label printer, High Quality label barcode printer, Resolution 203, printing speed 127mm/s (fast). Support various coding type print barcode coding system, support LOGO printing. Can print continuously, sequence of bar code can be set to special change. Repair rate is low, the quality stable and reliable. Automatic paper location function Built-in power supply. more safe and save space. Specifications Printer Specifications Print Method Direct thermal line Resolution 203 dpi Print Width Max 76mm Print Speed 2 ~ 5inch/s Interface USB + Serial Print head temperature detect Thermal sensitive ressistance Print Head Position detect Mircoswitch Paper sensor Photoelectric sensor Memory DRAM: 8M FLASH: 4M Command set TSPL Media Characteristics Paper Type Thermal paper, Thermal label, Adhesive thermal paper Media Width 25-82mm Media Diameter 25 ~ 100mm Paper Off Type Tear off BarCode/Fonts/ Graphics Symbologies Enlargement&amp;Rotation 1 ~10 times enlargement in both directions; 0 、 90 、 270 、 360 rotation Character Size Font 0 ~ Font 8 1D Barcode Code39, Code93, Code128 subsets A, B, C, Codabar, Interleaved 2 of 5, EAN-13, EAN-14, EAN-128, UPC-A, UPC-E, EAN and UPC 2(5) digits add-on, MSI, PLESSEY, POSTNET, china POS, ITF14 Graphics Processing Support BMP/PCX/BAS files Editing Software Nicelabel SE Operating Characteristics Cashdrawer Out 24VDC/2A Power Supply AC 110V/220V, 50 ~ 60Hz, DC 24V/2A Work Environment Temperature: 5~45 (41~104 ), Humidity: 25~85%RH Storage Environment Temperature: -10~50 (-10~140 ), Humidity: 10%~90%RH Physical Characteristics Weight 1.5kg Dimension 227×152×143mm</description>
			       <g:price>7500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>GT3120TUB</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/Presentatiozn2.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE PRINTER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Fingerprint Access Control Jun Rong M868D Time Attendance </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/fingerprint-access-control-jun-rong-m868d-time-attendance.html</link>
			       <description>Best Quality Fingerprint Access Control Jun Rong M868D Time Attendance CPU: 32-bit ARM7 Algorithm version: "JR Finger" F5.0</description>
			       <g:price>11000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>M868D</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/attendance_868d.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>TIME ATTENDANCE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> ZKTeco uFace302 Multi-Biometric T&amp;A Access Control Terminal </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zkteco-uface302-multi-biometric-access-control-terminal.html</link>
			       <description>Description : ZKTeco uFace302 Multi-Biometric T&amp;A Access Control Terminal ZKTeco uFace302 Multi-Biometric T&amp;A Access Control Terminal is made with High verification speed, Advanced and user-friendly UI and Chip encryption for firmware protection with 4.3-Inch Touch Screen. This access control terminal is One face template and it registered for one user only. It is to detect whether the face is an actual face or a photo and enhancing the security level of verification with Multi-languages and High verification speed. It has 193.6*165.2*86mm (Length*Width*Thickness) dimension, 1.6 kg weight, Operating Temperature 0 C- 45 C and Operating Humidity 20%-80%. In this terminal, It has Face capacity 1,200 (1:N), Fingerprint capacity 2000, ID Card capacity 10,000 (optional) and Logs capacity 100,000.This terminal added some Standard Functions like Automatic Status Switch, Self-Service Query, Work Code, SMS, DST, T9 Input, 9 Digit User ID, Scheduled Bell, Photo ID with 3rd Party Electric Lock, Door Sensor, Exit Button, Alarm interface. The ZKTeco latest hardware platform and algorithm, which provide clients with a brandnew UI and user-friendly operating interface, bringing them a smooth using experience. With the advanced face algorithm and multi-biometric verification technology, the terminal’s security level of verification is greatly enhanced.</description>
			       <g:price>20000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>uFace302</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/Zkteco_iface302_Time_Attendance_Terminal_dreamtechcombd-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>TIME ATTENDANCE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> ZKTeco MB300 Multi-Bio Time Attendance Terminal </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zkteco-mb300-multi-bio-time-attendance-terminal.html</link>
			       <description>Description : ZKTeco MB300 Multi-Bio Time Attendance Terminal with Adapter Face 400 Fingerprint Capacity 500 ID Card Capacity 1,000 Log Capacity 80,000 2.8-inch TFT Screen TCP/IP,USB-host (01 Year Warranty)</description>
			       <g:price>13000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>MB300</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/ZKTeco_MB300.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>TIME ATTENDANCE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> ZKTeco MB160 Fingerprint Reader Face Recognition System </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zkteco-mb160-face-finger-recognition-system.html</link>
			       <description>ZKTeco MB160 Fingerprint Reader Face Recognition System Specification: Main Features Fingerprint Capacity 2000 Face Capacity 1500 ID Card Capacity 2000 Record Capacity 100000 Display 2.8-inch TFT Screen Communication TCP/IP, USB-Host, Wi-Fi (Optional) Standard Functions SMS, DTS, Scheduled-bell, Self-Service Query, Automatic Status Switch, T9 Input, Photo ID, Camera, Multi-verification, 12V Output, RS232 Printer (Optional Cable) Interface 3rd Party Electric Lock, Exit Button, Alarm Others Verification Speed : 1Sec. Operating Temp. : 0 c - 45 c Operating Humidity : 20% - 80% Physical Specification Dimension 167.5 x 148.8 x 32.2 mm (Length*Width*Thickness) Power Supply DC 12V 1.5A Manufacture Warranty Warranty 01 year warranty Description : ZKTeco MB160 Fingerprint Reader Face Recognition System MB160 is an innovative product featured with ZK advanced fingerprint and face recognition technologies. It supports multiple verification methods including face, fingerprint, card, password, combinations between them and basic access control functions. User verification is performed in less than 0.5 seconds, which streamlines the process of access. The communication between the MB160 and PC is by TCP / IP or USB interface for manual data transfer. Its sleek design fits perfectly in any environment. This device comes with 01 years of warranty service.</description>
			       <g:price>15000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>MB160</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/ZKTeco_MB160_Fingerprint_Reader_Face_Recognition_System.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>TIME ATTENDANCE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> ZKTeco F22 WiFi Bio Metric Time Attendance </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zkteco-f22-wifi-bio-metric-time-attendance.html</link>
			       <description>ZKTeco F22 WiFi Bio Metric Time Attendance and Access controller Product Description: F22 is an ultra-thin fingerprint time attendance and access control terminal with BioID sensor and Wi-Fi, which offers unparalleled performance with advanced algorithm for reliability, precision and excellent matching speed.</description>
			       <g:price>10000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>ZKTeco F22</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/zkf22_access_www_dreamtechcombd-min-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>TIME ATTENDANCE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> ZK F18 Access Control And Time Attendance </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zk-f18-access-control-and-time-attendance.html</link>
			       <description>ZKteco F18 Access Control And Time Attendance Description: F18 is an innovative biometric fingerprint reader for access control applications, offering unparalleled performance using an advanced algorithm for reliability, precision and excellent matching speed. The F18 features the fastest commercial-based fingerprint matching algorithm and ZK high-performance, high-image quality optical fingerprint sensor. The device offers the flexibility to be installed standalone or with any third party panel that supports 26-bit Wiegand. All the operation can be done on the TFT-LCD. The fingerprint image will display on the screen . That will guide the user to put the finger on to proper position and increase the recognition rate. TCP/IP and RS485 are available that the device can be used in different network. Features: Fingerprint reader with durable and highly accurate ZK optical sensor 1 touch a-second user recognition Stores 3,000 templates,100,000 transactions Reads Fingerprint and/or Card Optional integrated smart card reader Built-in Serial and Ethernet ports Tamper-proofs switch and alarm outputs Request-to-exit and alarm contacts Audio-Visual indications for acceptance and rejection of valid/invalid fingers Specifications: Model F18 Software ZKAccess3.5 Display 2.4-inch TFT LCD Color Screen Fingerprint sensor ZK Optical Sensor Algorithm Version ZKFinger V10.0 Fingerprint Capacity 3,000 Card Capacity 10,000 Log Capacity 100,000 RF Card EM(standard)/MF(optional) Authentication Method FP only, RF only, PIN only, FP/RF/PIN, PIN&amp;FP, PIN&amp;RF Access Control Interface Electric lock, Door sensor, Alarm, Exit button Communication TCP/IP, RS232/485,USB-host Wiegand Signal Input,Output,SRB Functions DST,Record Query,Anti-passback,External RS485 fingerprint reader,Printer(Optional) Power Supply 12VDC 3A Operating Temperature 0~ 45 Dimensions (W×H×D) 80mm×183mm×42mm</description>
			       <g:price>8500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>1877</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/zkf18.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>TIME ATTENDANCE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> ZKTeco uFace602 Face Biometric Attendance Machine </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zkteco-uface602-attendance-machine.html</link>
			       <description>Specification: Main Features Fingerprint Capacity 4000 Face Capacity 3000 ID Card Capacity 10000 Display 4.3 Inch Description : ZKTeco uFace602 Face Reader Biometric Attendance Machine ZKTeco UFace602 is basically a high end standalone Facial T&amp;A cum Access Control System. The reader has Touch Screen display which displays the EMPLOYEE NAME and ID. The image quality of the Facial is comparatively high as it can recognize images of faces with beard, cap, and bare heads the images are stored in the software's database for further use also. For multiple readers installed at a single location, the images can be replicated in multiple readers through the software.</description>
			       <g:price>22000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Face602</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/ZKTeco_UFace602_Face_Biometric__Machine.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>TIME ATTENDANCE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra Thermal transfer Wax Resin Ribbon 110mmX70m </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-thermal-transfer-wax-resin-ribbon-110mmx70m.html</link>
			       <description>Wax Resin Ribbon Thermal Transfer machine printer ribbon For Ribbon Printer Machine Brand ZEBRA Model GK888T.GC420 Color Black Material WAX Resin Option width 70mm Core(inch) 1", 1/2" Useage Used for all kinds of bar code printers Using environment 5 -35 / 45%-85%RH Customized Service Yes Applicable Medium PE, PET, BOPP, Hangtag, Cast-coated paper. Silver label Warranty 1 Year</description>
			       <g:price>800 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Z110x70m</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/wax_resin_110mmx70m.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra Thermal transfer wax ribbon 55mm X 300m </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-thermal-transfer-wax-ribbon-55mm-x-300m.html</link>
			       <description>Zebra Thermal transfer wax ribbon 55mm X 300m Features: Extensive label adaptability, good versatility. The printing effect is excellent, and the cost is economical and practical. High temperature resistance, suitable for high speed printing. Antistatic back coating is easy to protect print head effectively. Suitable for copper paper, label paper, polishing paper, rough paper, smoothing paper, synthetic paper, etc. Specifications: Color: Black Length: 300m Width: 60mm/ 90mm Type: Printer Ribbon Package included: 1 x Waxes Ribbon</description>
			       <g:price>350 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>1328336670</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/Barcode_Ribbon_55_mm_x_300m-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra Thermal transfer wax ribbon 220mmX300m </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-thermal-transfer-wax-ribbon-220mmx300m.html</link>
			       <description>Zebra Thermal transfer wax ribbon 220mm X 300m Features: Extensive label adaptability, good versatility. The printing effect is excellent, and the cost is economical and practical. High temperature resistance, suitable for high speed printing. Antistatic back coating is easy to protect print head effectively. Suitable for copper paper, label paper, polishing paper, rough paper, smoothing paper, synthetic paper, etc. Specifications: Color: Black Length: 300m Width: 60mm/ 90mm Type: Printer Ribbon Package included: 1 x Waxes Ribbon</description>
			       <g:price>1900 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Z220X300</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/ZEBRA_RIBBON_220_X300_M_BLACK-.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra Thermal transfer wax ribbon 110mmX70m </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-thermal-transfer-wax-ribbon-110mmx70m.html</link>
			       <description>Zebra Thermal transfer wax ribbon 110mm X 70m Features: Extensive label adaptability, good versatility. The printing effect is excellent, and the cost is economical and practical. High temperature resistance, suitable for high speed printing. Antistatic back coating is easy to protect print head effectively. Suitable for copper paper, label paper, polishing paper, rough paper, smoothing paper, synthetic paper, etc. Specifications: Color: Black Length: 70m Width: 110mm Type: Printer Ribbon Package included: 1 x Waxes Ribbon</description>
			       <g:price>430 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Z110X70</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/Barcode_Sticker_110x70-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> 80mm*60mm blank thermal paper rolls for shopping mall </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/80mm-60mm-blank-thermal-paper-rolls-for-shopping-mall.html</link>
			       <description>80mm*60mm blank thermal paper rolls for shopping mall Product Description: Size 80*60 Gsm 45g-70g Core Cardboard or plastic, 13mm*18mm, 18mm*25mm etc MOQ 100 rolls Delivery Time within 2 days Payment terms Cash. Manufacture Made in Bangladesh.</description>
			       <g:price>90 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>80-60</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/80mm-60mm-blank-thermal-paper-rolls-for.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>unisex</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>60</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> L4 Wash Care Label for Zebra,Godex </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/l4-wash-care-label-for-zebra,godex.html</link>
			       <description>L4 Wash Care Label for Zebra,Godex,TSC wash care Label Printer Type L4 Wash care label Color Pantone color,CMYK Core size 1inch,3inch Label Dimension Customized size Label Shape Customized Die cut shape Material Cloth Application Bags ,garment ,shoes,suitcase accessories Feature Eco-friendly,washable Packing Rolls</description>
			       <g:price>250 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>L4 Wash</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/l4_care_label_2.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> 80mm*80mm Thermal paper rolls </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/80mm-80mm-thermal-paper-rolls.html</link>
			       <description>80mm*80mm thermal paper rolls for POS/ATM with high quality Product Description: Size 80*80 Gsm 45g-70g Core Cardboard or plastic, 13mm*18mm, 18mm*25mm etc MOQ 100 rolls Delivery Time within 2 days Payment terms Cash. Manufacture Made in Bangladesh.</description>
			       <g:price>120 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>80-80</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/pos_roll_thermal_3_1.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra Thermal transfer wax ribbon 55mmX70m </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-thermal-transfer-wax-ribbon-55mmx70m.html</link>
			       <description>Zebra Thermal transfer wax ribbon 55mm X 70m Features: Extensive label adaptability, good versatility. The printing effect is excellent, and the cost is economical and practical. High temperature resistance, suitable for high speed printing. Antistatic back coating is easy to protect print head effectively. Suitable for copper paper, label paper, polishing paper, rough paper, smoothing paper, synthetic paper, etc. Specifications: Color: Black Length: 70m Width: 55mm Type: Printer Ribbon Package included: 1 x Waxes Ribbon</description>
			       <g:price>380 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Z55X70</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/Barcode_Sticker_55x70-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> HIKVISION 1.0MP Fixed Indoor Turret Camera </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/hikvision-ds-2ce56c0t-irpf-1-0mp-dome-camera.html</link>
			       <description>1 MP Fixed Indoor Turret Camera Specification: Camera Lens Field of view: 70.9 (3.6 mm), 92 (2.8 mm), 56.7 (6 mm) Lens Mount M12 Day &amp; Night ICR Synchronization Internal synchronization Angle Adjustment Pan: 0 to 360 , Tilt: 0 to 75 , Rotation: 0 to 360 Effective Pixels 1296 (H) × 732 (V) S/N Ratio  62 dB Image Sensor 1 MP CMOS image sensor Signal System PAL/NTSC Frame Rate 720p@25fps/720p@30fps Min. Illumination 0.01 Lux@(F1.2, AGC ON), 0 Lux with IR Shutter Time 1/25 (1/30) s to 1/50,000 s Interface Video Output 1 analog HD output General Operating Condition -40 C to 60 C (-40 F to 140 F), Humidity: 90% or less (non-condensation) Power Supply 12 V DC 15% Power Consumption Max. 4 W IR Range Up to 20 m Dimensions Φ 89.9 mm × 70.1 mm (3.54" × 2.76") Weight 250 g (0.55 lb.)</description>
			       <g:price>1100 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>2CE56C0T</g:id>
			       <g:image_link></g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>CCTV SOLUTION</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> SUNMI SCANNER HIGH SPEED QR 2D SCANNER </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/sunmi-scanner-high-speed-qr-2d-scanner.html</link>
			       <description>SUNMI SCANNER HIGH SPEED 1D QR 2D SCANNER Quick Scanning Fitted with a high-performance CMOS imaging chip and a soft white fill light that compliments its red focus beam, the SUNMI Scanner can quickly capture bar codes on mobile screens and paper even in a poorly lit environment. Accurate Identification Assures Rapid Scanning Of Exception Codes The image decoding algorithm is fast enough to make an accurate reading of distorted and even wrinkled 1D/2D bar codes or payment codes. Unmatched Durability The scanner's button can take upto 3 million clicks The scanner complies with a 1.2 meter (4 feet) drop test Field of view angle horizontal 45 vertical 34 Sensor CMOS, 640×480 px OS Windows/Android/Linux Reading Depth of Field EAN13 13mil 55mm-300mm QR CODE 15mil 35mm-190mm Lighting White LED Dimensions 16cm×9.5cm×7.1cm Communication interface USB 2.0 TypeA male connector Focusing Red light LED 625nm Barcode Sensitivity Inclined 50 / Rotary 360 / Deflected 50 Symbol Contrast 30% Prompt method Buzzer, vibrator LED prompt Environment Operating temperature -10 ~50 Storage temperature -40 ~+70 Relative humidity 5%~95%(no condensation) Electrostatic protection 8kV(direct discharge) 15kV(air discharge) Drop height 1.2meters Symbologies 1D Code128, UCC/EAN-128, AIM128, EAN-8, EAN-13, ISBN/ISSN, UPC-E, UPC-A, Interleaved 2 of 5, ITF-6, ITF-4, Matrix 2 of 5, Industrial 25, Standard 25, Code39, Codabar, Code 93, Code 11, Plessey, MSI-Plessey, RSS-14、 RSS-Limited、RSS-Expand 2D PDF417 QR Code Data Matrix * One Year Warranty.</description>
			       <g:price>4800 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>SUNMI SCANNER</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/sunmi-ns021-1d-2d-reader.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebex Z-3220 Barcode Scanner </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebex-z-3220-barcode-scanner.html</link>
			       <description>Zebex Z-3220 Barcode Scanner Description : Type: Barcode Scanner Resolution: 2,500 pixel linear sensor Bar Code Scan Speed: 150 scans per second Image Sensor: N/A Light Source: 625 nm visible LED Interface: Keyboard, RS-232, HID USB, USB Virtual COM, wand, OPOS, JPOS Scan Size: N/A Dimention: 161.5 x 72.5 x 55.2 mm Warranty 1 year</description>
			       <g:price>2900 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Zebex_Z-3220</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/Zebex_Z-3220_Barcode_Scanner_slice.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> 1D Barcode Scanner Reader Handheld C520 </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/1d-barcode-scanner-reader-handheld-c520.html</link>
			       <description>Plug In Play 1D Barcode Scanner Reader Handheld C520 Product description Plug and play, read all the standard 1D bar codes Handheld type barcode scanner is with USB port cable, LED and buzzer indicator. Very comfortable operation sense, Intelligent AGC control, Rich decoded types. Safty performance: According with national level 2 laser safty standars Operational Light Source:Visible 650-670nm Depth of Field:0-600mm(0.33mm.PCS90%) Reading Distance:2.5-600mm(100% UPC/EAN) Print Contrast:30% min Scan Scope:10mm-250mm Work with all versions of Windows, Mac and Linux Works with Quickbook, Word, Excel, Novell, and all common software No software needed, it's plug and play USB barcode scanner that can read all the standard 1D bar codes like 1D UPS, USPS, FedEx, DHL, BOOK barcode. Only work on device that has USB port, not for iPad, google tablet, smart phone etc Can't read any barcode from Screen. Can't read any type 2D barcode like QR code PDF417 etc.</description>
			       <g:price>2400 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>C520</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/1D_Laser_Barcode_Scanner_C520_.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> uFace 800 Time Attendance And Access Control </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/~oaosknmp/product/uface-800-time-attendance-and-access-control.html</link>
			       <description>uFace 800 Face Time Attendance And Access Control Specification Display 4.3-Inch Touch Screen Face capacity 3,000 Fingerprint capacity 4,000 ID Card capacity 10,000 (Optional) Logs capacity 100,000 Communication TCP/IP, USB Host, Wi-Fi(optional) Standard Functions Automatic Status Switch, Self-Service Query, Work Code, SMS, DST, T9 Input, 9 Digit User ID, Scheduled Bell, Photo ID Optional Functions Mi Fare Card, 3G, ADMS, 2000mAH Backup Battery Power Supply 12V 3A Operating Temperature 0 C- 45 C Operating Humidity 20%-80% Dimensions 193.6*165*111mm (Length*Width*Thickness) Package Weight 1.87 kg</description>
			       <g:price>19500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Face-800</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/~oaosknmp/images/Zkteco_iface302_Time_Attendance_Terminal_dreamtechcombd-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>TIME ATTENDANCE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Electronic Barcode weighing Scale </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/~oaosknmp/product/electronic-barcode-weighing-scale.html</link>
			       <description>Electronic Barcode weighing Scale 15KG Highst Wet 1. Supermarket electronic label barcode scale, Electronic Barcode weighing Scale Water-proof, moisture-proof, insect-resistant. Avoid bugs crawl into the machine, and all kinds of malfunctions causes such as wet. 2. Exquisite ,with drawable printer,easy to take out paper and replace paper, simple and convenient operation. 3. Support PLU updating on line and editing, ensure the item all the latest information. 4. Storage capacity up to 10000 pieces commodities and support 224 hotkeys. Set menu shortcuts, through the PC software can adjust the hotkey sequence and print it out. 5. Each item could choose any tag format independently. Multiple barcode optional,eg, 8bit,13 bit, and 18 bit. 6. Can set up different types and information, etc according to different items. It advantageous to the commodity classification management. 7. Support Labels and barcode rotated 90 degrees, or 270 degree printing. 8. Support of wan access, Software can be upgraded online, to meet customer’s special demand. 9. More rich label content. can print production date, date of packaging, fresh date, expiration date, Select it according to clients requirements. 10. Searching products quickly by product No. 11. Support discount schedule, discount period setting. 12. Support for multiple foreign languages, labels, Electronic Barcode weighing Scale, such as background, the name of the item etc. 13. Support double screen dot matrix display, easy to promote products. 14. Support receipt paper and label paper printing. 15. Dual-motor design, printing more efficient and stable.</description>
			       <g:price>33000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>weighing -15kg</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/~oaosknmp/images/demo/shop/products-list/digital-barcode-weighing-scales-with-rs232-and_1-min.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE PRINTER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> XPrinter XP-Q160II 80mm Thermal Receipt Printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/xprinter-xp-q160ii-80mm-thermal-receipt-printer.html</link>
			       <description>XPrinter XP-Q160II 80mm 3 Inch Thermal Receipt Printer Specification:</description>
			       <g:price>6500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>4554</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/xprinter.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>POINT OF SALE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Xprinter XP-Q160I USB Wired Bluetooth Printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/xprinter-xp-q160i-usb-wired-bluetooth-printer.html</link>
			       <description>Specification: Printing Method Direct Line Thermosensitivity Print width 72mm paper width Point density 576 points/row or 512 points/row Printing speed 160 mm/s Interface USB Printing paper 79.5 +0.5 mm *80 mm Line spacing 3.75 mm (line spacing can be adjusted by command) Column Number 80mm Paper: Font A - 42 Column or 48 Column / Font B - 56 Column or 64 Column / Simple, Traditional - 21 Column or 24 Column Character size ANK character, Font A: 1.5 *3.0mm (12 *24 points); Font B: 1.1 *2.1mm (9 *17 points); Simplified/Traditional: 3.0 *3.0mm (24 *24 points) Extended Character Table PC347 (Standard Europe), Katakana, and PC850 (Multilingual), PC860 (Portuguese), PC863 (Canadian-French), PC865 (Nordic), and Western Europe, Greek, Hebrew, East Europe, Iran, WPC1252, PC866 (Cyrillic 2), PC852 (Latin 2), PC858, IranII, Latvian, Arabic, PT151 (1251) Barcode type UPC-A/UPC-E/JAN13 (EAN13)/JAN8 (EAN8)/ CODE39/ITF/CODABAR/CODE93/CODE128 Input buffer 64k bytes NV Flash 256k bytes Power adapter input AC 110V/220V, 50-60Hz Power output DC 24V/2.5A Cash box output DC 24V/1A Weight 1.03 kg Size 190 × 140 × 131 mm Working environment temperature 0-45 C, humidity: 10-80% Storage environment temperature -10- 60 C, humidity: 10- 90% (no condensation)</description>
			       <g:price>6500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>5079</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/xprinter_18-.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>POINT OF SALE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> C561+P POS Machine Dual Screen </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/c561-p-pos-machine-dual-screen.html</link>
			       <description>C561+P POS Machine Dual Screen All In One P.O.S Terminal Motherboard Specifics: Model NO. ITX-3317U - i5 128G SSD CPU Integrated Intel 22NM I5 3317U Dual-Core CPU 1.7GHz TDP 17W Chipset Intel NM70 Chipset Memory 1* SO DDRIII 1333/1066MHz, Max. Up to 4GB Graphics Intel HD Graphics Offer 1* VGA,2* HDMI,1* LVDS (support dual 24bit) support HDMI1/VGA synchronous/asynchronous display support LVDS/VGA synchronous/asynchronous display support LVDS/HDMI1 synchronous/asynchronous display support HDMI1/HDMI2 synchronous/asynchronous display Expansion Slots 1* Mini-PCIE, support WIFI/3G 1* MSATA, support SSD 128Gbps/WIFI LAN 1* RTL8111E 10/100/1000Mbps Ethernet, Support Wake-on-LAN and PXE function Storage 2* SATAII 3Gbps Audio Integrated Realtek HD ALC662 for 6-Channel output Support MIC/Line-out/Line-in Rear I/O 4* USB 2.0 1* HDMI 1* VGA 1* RJ-45 LAN 1* Line out(green) 1* Mic (red) 1* 12V DC_JACK input Internal I/O 1* LVDS 2*15pin, support dual 24bit LCD 1* JHDMI 2*8Pin 1* JVGA1 2*5pin 6* RS232, COM2 and COM3 also support RS485/422 and 9PIN charged function. 1* TX-RXCOM (RS422/485) 2*5Pin 1* LPT 4* USB 2.0(If the Mini-PCIE is a USB signal, supports 2 USB) 1* PS/2 6Pin 1* FP1 (2*5pin Front panel buttons and LED connected) 1* AUDIO pin (Front Audio interface 2*5pin) 1* SIM 2* PWROUT (Hard drive power connector) 1* ATX_12V (Can be used as input and output 12V power connector) 1* LVDS INVERTER Fan interface 1* CPUFAN 4pin 1* SYSFAN 3pin GPIO 1* GPIO (Support 4-way GPIO function) BIOS AMI 32MB Flash ROM Watchdog Support hardware reset function (L256, 0~255 seconds) Power Input DC_12V Single power supply Operating Temp. -10 ~60 Storage Temp. -20 ~70 Humidity 0%-95%(relative humidity; non-condensing) Dimension 170mm x 170mm</description>
			       <g:price>45000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>4322</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/WeChat_Image_20190519130255.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>POINT OF SALE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Postek C168/300C 300 dpi barcode label thermal printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/postek-c168-300c-300-dpi-barcode-label-thermal-printer.html</link>
			       <description>Postek C168/300C 300 dpi barcode label thermal printer Features: Compact, affordable, endurance performance. Rigid structure, plus the highly reliable motor&amp; transmission system result in minimal down time and low service cost.</description>
			       <g:price>25000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>postekC168</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/postek_C168300C_300_dpi_dream_tech.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE PRINTER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra gk888t Barcode Printer For Gold </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-888t-barcode-printer-for-gold.html</link>
			       <description>Zebra GC420 Barcode Printer For Gold Price teg printer Specification Brand Zebra Model Zebra GK888T Printer Method Thermal Printing speed 4 inch/102 per sec Print Width 4.09 inch /104 mm Print Length 39 inch /990 mm Print resolution 203 dpi/8 dots per mm Paper width 1.00"/25.4 mm to 4.25"/108 mm Paper Thickness 0.003"/0.08 mm to 0.007"/0.18 mm Paper Type Roll-fed , fan fold ,Label, Tag , Receipt paper , Wristband Paper Sensor Reflective and transmissive sensors Interface (Built-in) USB , Serial ,Parallel Memory 8MB Dimensions 7.9"/201 mm , 6.8"/173 mm , 9.4"/239 mm Weight 3.2 lbs/1.5 kg Warranty 1 year</description>
			       <g:price>16500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Zebra GC420</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/Zebra_GC420_Barcode_Printer_For_Gold1_wwwdreamtechcombd-min-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE PRINTER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Cloud Label Printer GP-CL421D 4" Size </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/cloud-label-printer-gp-cl421d-4-size.html</link>
			       <description>Gprinter Cloud Label Printer GP-CL421D 4" Size Direct Transfer Label Printer Print Mode Direct thermal Print Speed 2-8 inch/s Interface USB+USB HOST+Ethernet Resolution 203dots/inch (8dots/mm) Dot Size 0.125x0.125mm (1mm=8dots) Print Width Max 104mm (4.09") Print Length 2286mm (90") Print Head Temperatur sensor: thermal sensitive ressistance Pisition sensor: microswith Memory DRAM: 2M FLASH: 2M Pulse excitation 1X10 8 Pulses Printer language EPL Media Paper Roll OD 130mm OD Paper Type Continuous paper , paper with interspaces , folding paper ,black mark paper etc. PaperRolling Up Method Printing side outward rolling Paper Width Max. 120mm (4.72") Min. 40mm (0.78") Paper Thickness Max. 0.254mm (10mil) Min. 0.06mm (2.36mil) Paper Roll Core Size 25.4mm~38mm (1"~1.5") Paper Gap Min. 2 mm (0.09") Label Length 10~2286mm (0.39"~90") Remark: If label length is less than 25.4mm(1 inch), the label paper with perforated line are recommended in order to tear off the labels easily. Physical properties Weight 2.09kg Dimension 285*210*180mm(W*D*H) Environment Work Environment Temperature: 5 ~ 45 , Humidity: 25 ~ 85% Storage Environment Temperature: -10 ~ 50 , Humidity: 10 ~ 90% Reliability Print head 30KM Power Power Supply The built-in voltage automatic switching power supply Input: AC 110V/240V, Output: 50 ~ 60Hz, Output:DC24V/2A.60W</description>
			       <g:price>24000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>9000</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/Cloud_Label_Printer_GPCL421D_4_Size__1_wwwdreamtechcombd-min-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE PRINTER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zkteco K40 Pro Time &amp; Attendance, Access Control </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zkteco-k40-pro-time-attendance,-access-control.html</link>
			       <description>Battery Backup Zkteco K40 Pro Time &amp; Attendance, Access Control Description : ZKTeco K40 is a 2.8-inch TFT screen Time Attendance &amp; Simple Access Control Terminal. It has interfaces for third party electric lock and exit button. TCP/IP and USB Host make data management extremely easy. Most importantly, the built-in backup battery can eliminate the trouble of power-failure. With elegant appearance and reliable quality, you can get the best from it. Special Feature of TCP/IP, USB-host ,Built-in battery,Simple access control or external bell, SSR report in excel forms. Specification: Fingerprint Capacity 1000 ID Card Capacity 1000 (Optional) Record Capacity 100,000 Display 2.8-Inch TFT Screen Communication TCP/IP, USB Host Standard Function Work Code, SMS, DST, Self-Service Query, Automatic Status Switch, Scheduled-Bell, T9 Input, 9 Digit User ID, Built-In Battery, Simple Access Control Or External Bell Optional Function ID/Mifare Software ZKTime5.0 Power Supply DC 12V 1.5A Verification Speed  0.5 Sec. Operating Temp 0 C-45 C Operating Humidity 20%-80% Dimension 184*136*37.6(Length*Width*Thickness) * One Year Warranty.</description>
			       <g:price>5500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>K40 Pro</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/ZKTECO_K40.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>TIME ATTENDANCE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Digital Persona U.are.U 4500 Bio metric </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/digital-persona-u-are-u-4500-bio-metric.html</link>
			       <description>Digital Persona U.are.U 4500 Bio metric For Bank sim registration Description: The U.are.U 4500 Fingerprint Reader is a USB peripheral perfect for individual desk top users, as well as multiple users in shared environments. Its compact design conserves desk space in enterprises, and its professional, modern appearance looks elegant in point-of-sale environments.The U.are.U 4500 Reader utilizes optical fingerprint scanning technology to achieve excellent image quality, a large capture area and superior reliability. A silicone coating allows it to read a wide range of fingerprints accurately and rapidly regardless of placement angle.The high-quality metal casing resists unintentional movement. To use, simply place a finger on the reader window and the reader quickly and automatically captures and encrypts the fingerprint image before sending it to the DigitalPersona FingerJet biometric engine for verification. For superior user feedback, a red “flash” indicates that a fingerprint image has been captured. The U.are.U 4500 Fingerprint Reader is designed for use with Digital Persona full range of software including our authentication solutions, DigitalPersona Pro Enterprise and DigitalPersona Online, as well as our U.are.U Software Development Kits (except for the U.are.U SDK for Android ). Whether you are an enterprise customer or a system integrator, Digital Persona’s biometric identity verification solutions provide a natural extension to your security system and applications. Specification: A.The thinnest optical fingerprint sensor in the world . B.URU4500 fingerprint scanner is 512 DPI . C. Free Original DigitalPersona SDK D.This portable USB fingerprint scanner supportJAVA development platform CB, VB, VC, Delphi, PB8, VBdemo, VFP, VB.net, C# , asp.net, PHP etc E.Driver support Windows98, Me, NT4.0,2000, XP, Vista, Windows Sever 2000,2003,2008,2010. F.It is compatible with all U.are.U applications and development tools to support Biokey Development Tools Product Specification Resolution : 512 DPI Image size: 14.6mm*18.1mm Interface USB1.1, compatible with USB1.0,1.1,2.0 full speed Sensor: Optical Sensor Compatible OS:Windows98,Me,NT4.0,2000,XP,Vista,7, 8, 10, Windows Sever 2000,2003,2008, 2010 Standard: FCC Class B, CE, ICES, BSMI, MIC, USB, WHQL, VCCI Picture image: 8-bit grayscale image data Operating Temperature: 0 C-45 C Operating Humidity: 20%-80% Supply voltage: 5.0V + /-0.25V USB offers Idle: 140mA (typical) Interface: 190mA (typical) Hangs: 1.5mA (max) Anti-static:   15 KV</description>
			       <g:price>7200 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>300</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/Digital-Persona-Optical-Biometrics-Fingerprint-Scanner.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>TIME ATTENDANCE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> ZK-X6 Fingerprint Access Controller Complete </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zk-x6-fingerprint-access-controller.html</link>
			       <description>ZK-X6 Fingerprint Keypad Access Controller Description ZKTeco zk-x6 fingerprint door lock access control system has up to 500 ID card capacity, up to 500 fingerprint capacity, up to 8 group password capacity, 125kHz RFID proximity reader and small rugged elegant access control design.</description>
			       <g:price>10200 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>950</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/ZK-X6_Fingerprint_Access_Controller_dreamtechcombd-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>TIME ATTENDANCE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> RFID Access Control System Kit (Wooden Glasses) </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/rfid-access-control-system-kit.html</link>
			       <description>RFID Access Control System Kit (Wooden Glasses) A.Supporting card,password,card+password to open door B.Offline work C.Power off data protection function D.Connect to the door bell by wire or wireless with accordance to customer requirement and support the switch for opening the door</description>
			       <g:price>450 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>5065</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/ACCESS_CONTROLLER_door_lock.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>TIME ATTENDANCE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Waterproof Barcode Wax-based Wax Resin </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/waterproof-barcode-wax-based-wax-resin.html</link>
			       <description>Waterproof Barcode Wax-based Wax Resin Description: Products: Thermal transfer ribbon Brand Name: Dmax Ink Side IN or OUT Material : Wax , Resin , Wax/Resin, Premium wax/resin Ribbon Color: Black,White,Gold,Red,Yellow,Blue,Green,Grey. Usage Humidity: 40%-80% Humidity Rate Storage Temperature: -5-49 Usage Temperature: 0-35 Storage Humidity: 25%-80% Humidity Rate Basic Width: 30mm,40mm,50mm,60mm,70mm,80mm,90mm,100mm,110mm or customized. Basic Length: 30m,74m, 90m,100m,300m,450m,600m,650m or customized. Core Size: 1 inch , 1/2 inch Matched Label Substrates: barcode label , thermal barcode labels Packaging: Packing in rolls Delivery Time: Within 7-15 days upon receipt of deposit Service: OEM service is available. Wax Ribbon application Substrates for Semi-gloss coated paper, thermal paper, woodfree paper, kraft paper, tag, price labels. Wax Resin application Substrates for Semi gloss coated paper, thermal paper, woodfree paper, kraft paper, tag, price labels, matte coated paper, PP synthetic paper, Resin Ribbon application Substrates for Semi -gloss coated paper, PET, PVC, PE, PP, etc. Remarks: Ribbon width should be about 10mm wider than sticker size and narrower than max print width</description>
			       <g:price>750 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Wax_Resin</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/zebra_color_ribbon.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra Thermal transfer wax ribbon 110mm 300m </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-thermal-transfer-wax-ribbon-110mm-300m.html</link>
			       <description>Zebra Thermal transfer wax ribbon 110mm 300m Features: Extensive label adaptability, good versatility. The printing effect is excellent, and the cost is economical and practical. High temperature resistance, suitable for high speed printing. Antistatic back coating is easy to protect print head effectively. Suitable for copper paper, label paper, polishing paper, rough paper, smoothing paper, synthetic paper, etc. Specifications: Color: Black Length:300m Width: 60mm/ 90mm Type: Printer Ribbon Package included: 1 x Waxes Ribbon</description>
			       <g:price>500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>300m</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/ribbon_1.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> POS Cash Register Receipt Roll For 58mm Thermal Printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/pos-cash-register-receipt-roll-for-58mm-thermal-printer.html</link>
			       <description>POS Cash Register Receipt Roll For 58mm Thermal Printer Description: Type: Thermal Paper</description>
			       <g:price>45 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>58 mm</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/pos_roll_thermal_1_.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> 57*35 blank thermal cash register paper rolls </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/57-35-blank-thermal-cash-register-paper-rolls.html</link>
			       <description>57mm*35 mm blank thermal paper rolls for shopping mall Product Description: Size 57*35 Gsm 45g-70g Core Cardboard or plastic, 13mm*18mm, 18mm*25mm etc MOQ 100 rolls Delivery Time within 2 days Payment terms Cash. Manufacture Made in Bangladesh.</description>
			       <g:price>30 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>57-35</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/POS_BOX.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Wax Resin Thermal Transfer Mixed Printer Ribbon </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/wax-resin-thermal-transfer-mixed-printer-ribbon.html</link>
			       <description>Thermal transfer ribbon for printing labels Description Specification Ink material Wax/Resin/Wax Resin Color Black Base film Polyester film Heat resistance coating Silicon base Base film thickness 4.5u Total thickness 7.5u 0.5u Print density 1.5 Print speed 2~12IPS Print sensitivity 8.5 Heat resistance 6 Scratch resistance 8 Solvent resistance 7 Label adaptability 10 Use environment 5 C~35 C,20%~85%RH Storage environment -5 C~40 C,20%~85%RH</description>
			       <g:price>900 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>dnp-101</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/dmax_ribbon.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Thermal Paper 57x50mm Thermal Receipt Paper </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/thermal-paper-57x50mm-thermal-receipt-paper.html</link>
			       <description>Thermal Cash Register Paper 57 mm x 50 mm Roll Suitable for Mobile 58 mm mini thermal printer! High brightness. Minimized dust. Size:57*50(mm) Package included:1 * Thermal Paper Minimum Order- 50 Pcs</description>
			       <g:price>45 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Roll 57x50mm</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/pos_roll_1.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Mobile POS 58mm Thermal Printer Roll 50*57 mm </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/mobile-pos-58mm-thermal-printer-roll.html</link>
			       <description>Mobile POS 58mm Thermal Printer Roll 50*57 mm Description: Type: Thermal printing paper</description>
			       <g:price>45 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Printer Roll</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/pos_roll_thermal_.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Thermal Paper Roll 80x70 mm </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/thermal-paper-roll-80x70-mm.html</link>
			       <description>Thermal Paper Roll 80x70 mm 60 gsm paper Description: Thermal Receipt paper 80x70 is the most popular receipt paper size used in supermarket, shopping malls thermal paper, resaurants thermal paper, coffee shops thermal paper, office buildings thermal paper. Width: 80mm Diameter: 70mm Core: 13mm Packing: 50 Rolls/Carton If Big Order Than- POS paper roll price -Is Less.</description>
			       <g:price>100 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>80x70 mm</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/pos_roll_thermal_2_1.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> USB Bar Code Scanner RS232 Reader Barcode Reading Gun </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/usb-bar-code-scanner-rs232-reader-barcode-reading-gun.html</link>
			       <description>USB Bar Code Scanner RS232 Reader Barcode Reading Gun Features: USB interface, simple installation. You can setting your scanner from the PC keyboard or scanning. Auto detecting the type of computer. Support over twenty different countries keyboard layout. Reading or Not-Reading indicate by LED light and buzzer. Low power consumption. Specifications: Barcode Type: Standard 1D Barcode Scan Model: Single Line, Bi-directional Scan Speed: 120 times/sec Indication: LED Light, Buzzer Lifetime of Using: Over 5,000,000 Times Package Size: 17 * 10.5 * 8cm / 6.7 * 4.1 * 3.1in Package Weight: 234g / 8.3oz Package List: 1 * Barcode Scanner 1 * USB Cable 1 * English User Manual</description>
			       <g:price>10500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Reading_Gun</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/DMAX_x718_c.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Honeywell Barcode Scanner Youjie Hand Held YJ3300 -White </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/honeywell-barcode-scanner-youjie-hand-held-yj3300-white.html</link>
			       <description>Honeywell Barcode Scanner Youjie Hand Held YJ3300 -White color Description : The Honeywell YJ3300 is an affordable hand-held laser barcode scanner that offers an alternative to CCD scanners. Its functional ergonomic design enables itself to fit in a wide variety of applications. The Honeywell YJ3300 is the best choice for customers who are seeking to create paperless offices or who care to replace their current existing devices with a high-quality and cost-saving barcode scanner.Equipped with world-class laser decoding technology, the Honeywell YJ3300 can be applied in a variety of environments.The Honeywell YJ3300’s pulsing-laser-line switch allows the user to easily target the desired barcode and complete data transmission with just the press of a button. This makes the Honeywell YJ3300 the optimal choice for menu scanning, point-of-sale, document processing, and inventory control. With improved laser scanning technology, the Honeywell YJ3300 has a longer working range and a wider scan field than a typical CCD. The width of the scan line grows as the scanner moves further away from the bar code.The ergonomic trigger and handle of the Honeywell YJ3300 fits comfortably in any user’s hands and provides easy to use operation. Additionally, the pulsing-laser-line switch design decreases the continuous operating time of the laser engine, thus increasing the time efficiency and reliability of the scanner. Integrated with a common interface, the YJ3300 ensures fast and easy connections with the host or PC.</description>
			       <g:price>3400 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>50100</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/YJ3300_-White.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Datalogic Heron usb 1d 2d bar code qr code </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/datalogic-heron-usb-1d-2d-bar-code-qr-code.html</link>
			       <description>Datalogic Heron 3400 HD3430 usb 1d 2d bar code qr code portable hand held barcode scanner with USB cable FEATURES Outstanding reading performance on 1D, 2D, postal codes, stacked and composite codes Innovative and unique design raises the bar for a cutting-edge POS checkout experience In-mold decorated top cover with ‘carbon-fiber’ or ‘silver’ look Multiple changing color LEDs on sides and top Polyphonic speaker for a wide variety of choices regarding audio feedback Easily customized with logo, top cover, visual and audio feedback Datalogic’s patented ‘Green Spot’ technology for good-read feedback Automatic switching between handheld and hands-free operations Efficient illumination and aiming system EASEOFCARE Service Plans offer a wide range of service options to protect your investment, ensuring maximum productivity and ROI</description>
			       <g:price>28000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Heron</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/Datalogic-Heron-3400-HD3430-usb-1d-2d_hd.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra Symbol DS9808 Imager Barcode Scanner </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-symbol-ds9808-imager-barcode-scanner.html</link>
			       <description>Zebra Symbol DS9808 Imager Barcode Scanner Description: NEXT-GENERATION HYBRID PRESENTATION IMAGER Achieve a new level of productivity and throughput at the checkout stand with the Symbol DS9808. Designed to deliver a new level of versatility, functionality and performance, the DS9808 features a one-of-a-kind hybrid form factor that provides superior comfort and ease of use in both handheld and hands-free scanning modes.</description>
			       <g:price>23000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>50102</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/Symbol_DS9808_2D_Barcode_Scanner_dreamtechcombd-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Honeywell Eclipse MS5145 Barcode Scanner </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/honeywell-eclipse-ms5145-barcode-scanner.html</link>
			       <description>Honeywell Eclipse MS5145 Barcode Scanner very faster Description : The Honeywell MK5145-31A38 Eclipse MS5145 barcode reader is black, comes with a USB cable, and can be used to scan and decode linear one-dimensional (1D) barcodes. A laser produces a single line of light that can scan barcodes at a speed of up to 72 scans per second in continuous mode. A CodeGate setting allows the scan line to be visible but prevents barcode data from being transmitted until a button is pushed to help reduce accidental scans. The CodeSense feature automatically awakes the barcode scanner when a barcode is detected. The barcode reader’s USB cable can be plugged into the USB port of a computer or another host system (sold separately) to transmit barcode data. A configuration utility allows the firmware to be updated as needed to take advantage of new improvements or features. This product is compatible with OPOS (OLE for Retail POS) and JavaPOS standards used in point-of-sale (POS) systems. The barcode reader weighs 3.5 oz. and measures 2 x 2.5 x 6.7 inches (H x W x D). (H is height, the vertical distance from the lowest to highest point; W is width, the horizontal distance from left to right; D is depth, the horizontal distance from front to back.) It can withstand drops of up to 5′ on a concrete floor. A stand (sold separately) enables the barcode reader to be used in a fixed position. Barcode scanners, also known as barcode readers, can be used to scan and decode barcodes and to transmit barcode data to a computer or another host system. Barcode readers with a single-line laser can be used to scan linear, one-dimensional (1D) barcodes. Some lasers can produce light in an omnidirectional pattern to allow scanning of barcodes from different angles. Other barcode readers contain CCD (charge-coupled device) light sensors instead of a laser for accuracy and wear resistance. Barcode scanners with raster scanning, area imaging, and other scanning technologies can allow scanning of two-dimensional (2D) or Portable Document Format 417 (PDF417) barcodes, among other types. Some barcode readers provide onboard flash memory to allow the storage of barcode data before transmitting it to a computer or host system through a USB cable or wireless WLAN or Bluetooth connection. Many barcode readers have a handle for handheld use and come with a stand or a charging cradle for fixed position applications, while others are designed for stationary use on a counter or another flat surface. Some portable readers are small enough to be carried in a pocket or attached to a lanyard. Barcode readers are used at retail checkout counters and other points of sale (POS) locations and in warehouses and shipping facilities.</description>
			       <g:price>4200 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>909</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/Honeywell_Eclipse_5145_Barcode_Scanner_dreamtechcombd-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra Symbol DS4308 Handheld Scanner </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-symbol-ds4308-handheld-scanner.html</link>
			       <description>Symbol DS4308 Handheld Scanner If you’re looking for extraordinary flexibility and performance in your handheld scanner, the next-generation scanning technology in the DS4308 delivers. Its truly extraordinary range does the job of two scanners, allowing you to scan nearer and farther than any other scanner in this class. Your workers can scan virtually any barcode. The DS4308 does it all — 1-D or 2-D, electronic or printed on paper labels or plastic cards, even if the barcode is dirty, scratched or poorly printed. With PRZM Intelligent Imaging inside, your workers can capture barcodes as fast as they can pull the scan trigger. And that means no more Point-of-Sale exceptions that can turn into longer lines, longer wait times and lost sales. The DS4308 — a new class of scanner for a new world of barcodes.</description>
			       <g:price>13500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>zebra 4308</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/zebra_4308_2d.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Honeywell 1D 2D Youjie HF600 Scanner </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/honeywell-1d-2d-youjie-hf600-scanner.html</link>
			       <description>2d hands-free barcode scanner used in pos system Honeywell Youjie HF600 Ergonomic Design: 2-modular body design with large window can easily meet various scanning needs Switch for Mobile Scanning: a single button enables the optimal scanning of 2D barcodes on mobile phones,improving efficiency and customer satisfaction</description>
			       <g:price>15000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Youjie HF600</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/Honeywell-HF600-2d.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Honeywell Voyager 1202G Wireless Single-Line Barcode Scanner </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/honeywell-voyager-1202g-wireless-single-line-barcode-scanner.html</link>
			       <description>Honeywell Voyager 1202G Wireless Single-Line Barcode Scanner Bluetooth Wireless Technology: Facilitates scanning of all standard 1D bar codes 10 meters (33 feet) or more away from the base, depending on the user’s environment Long Battery Life and Tool-Free Battery Removal: The user-preferred Lithium ion battery provides 12 hours or more of use, depending on scanning volume, and the field-replaceable battery can be exchanged quickly and easily, without the use of tools</description>
			       <g:price>17000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>1202G</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/1202g.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra Symbol DS3678 heavy industrial bar code reader </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-symbol-ds3678-heavy-industrial-bar-code-reader.html</link>
			       <description>Zebra Symbol DS3678 SR 1D 2D imager scanner heavy industrial barcode reader The Symbol DS3578 Series of rugged, cordless, omni-directional 1-D/2-D imager scanners bring comprehensive, high-performance data capture to harsh industrial environments. Engineered with breakthrough digital imaging technology, this scanner family delivers extremely fast and accurate data capture of 1-D/2-D barcodes, direct part marks (DPM) and images, and supports Item Unique Identification (IUID). Integrated Bluetooth provides cordless freedom, improving productivity. Three models are available: DS3678-SR: 1-D/2-D barcodes DS3678-HD: 1-D/2-D barcodes; optimized to capture very small, high-density 2-D barcodes DS3678-DP: 1-D/2-D barcodes; DPM marks; IUID support.</description>
			       <g:price>45000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>DS3678</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/Zebra-Symbol-DS3678-SR-1D-2D-imager.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> UROVO i6300 with 1D/2D scan engine, 8MP front camera </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/urovo-i6300-with-1d-2d-scan-engine,-8mp-front-camera.html</link>
			       <description>UROVO i6300 Portable Terminal with 1D/2D scan engine, 8MP front camera Best-in-class durability Urovo i6300 — a full touch, Android-based, rugged, mobile computer - is your go-to assistant for any data capture purpose. This easy-to-use device eliminates all paper-based work and speeds up data recording, thus reducing errors and increasing work efficiency and productivity. maximum 128GB micro SD card Bluetooth 4.1 + BR/EDR + BLE Micro USB USB port, 3.5mm audio port, POGO pin</description>
			       <g:price>35000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>i6300</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/Urovo-i6300-1D.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra DS2208 1D Handheld Bar code Scanner </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-ds2208-sr-corded-2d-1d-handheld-barcode-scanner.html</link>
			       <description>Zebra Symbol DS2208 1D Handheld Bar code Scanner Description Zebra DS2208 Scanner, - USB Kit, Corded Area Imager, Standard Range. Color: Black. Includes USB cable. AFFORDABILITY AND SIMPLICITY DELIVERED 2D barcodes have made their way to your Point of Sale, appearing on everything from the items your customers are purchasing to printed and electronic coupons and loyalty cards. Barcode Scanner Your 1D scanner can’t capture the new 2D codes, leading to exceptions that slow down the check-out process and frustrate customers at that key last personal touchpoint in your store. But with the DS2200 Series, you can scan it all. You get an affordable 1D/2D imager that doesn’t compromise performance or features for price. Your workers get best-in-class first-time, every-time scanning with point-and-shoot simplicity. You get an imager that couldn’t be easier to deploy and manage. Dimensions Corded DS2208: 6.5 in. H x 2.6 in. W x 3.9 in. D 16.5 cm. H x 6.6 cm. W x 9.9 cm. D Cordless DS2278: 6.9 in. H x 2.6 in. W x 3.9 in. D 17.5 cm. H x 6.6 cm. W x 9.9 cm. D Presentation Cradle: 2.8 in. H x 3.7 in. W x 4.8 in. D 7.1 cm. H x 9.4 cm. W x 12.2 cm. D Weight Corded DS2208: 5.7 oz. / 161.6 g Cordless DS2278: TBD Presentation Cradle: TBD Input Voltage Range DS2208/DS2278 and Cradle: 4.5 to 5.5 VDC Host Powered; 4.5 to 5.5 VDC External Power Supply Current Corded DS2208 Operating Current at Nominal Voltage (5.0V): 250 mA (typical). (Note: Auto-Aim and Illumination on Acquiring Image) Corded DS2208 Standby Current (idle) at Nominal Voltage (5.0V): 150 mA (typical). (Note: Auto-Aim On) Presentation Cradle and Micro USB Cable: 500 mA (typical) Standard USB; 1100 mA (typical) BC 1.2 USB Color Nova White, Twilight Black Supported Host Interfaces USB, RS232, Keyboard Wedge, TGCS (IBM) 46XX over RS485 Keyboard Support Supports over 90 international keyboards User Indicators Direct Decode Indicator; good decode LEDs; Rear view LEDs; beeper (adjustable tone and volume) PERFORMANCE CHARACTERISTICS Motion Tolerance (Handheld) Up to 5 in./13 cm. per second for 13 mil UPC Swipe Speed (Hands-Free) Up to 30.0 in./76.2 cm. per second for 13 mil UPC Light Source Aiming Pattern: Linear 624nm Amber LED Illumination (2) 645nm Super-Red LEDs Imager Field of View 32.8 H x 24.8 V Nominal Image Sensor 640 x 480 pixels Minimum Print Contrast 25% minimum reflective difference Skew/Pitch/Roll Tolerance +/- 65 ; +/- 65 ; 0-360 Minimum Element Resolution Code 39 — 4.0 mil; Code 128 — 4.0 mil; Data Matrix — 6.0 mil; QR Code — 6.7 mil USER ENVIRONMENT Operating Temperature DS2208/DS2278 Imagers: 32.0 to 122.0 F/0.0 to 50.0 C Presentation Cradle: 32.0 to 104.0 F/0.0 to 40.0 C Storage Temperature -40.0 to 158.0 F/-40.0 to 70.0 C Humidity 5% to 95% RH, non-condensing Drop Specification Designed to withstand multiple drops at 5.0 ft./1.5 m to concrete Tumble Specification Designed to withstand 250 tumbles in 1.5 ft./.5 m tumbler1 Environmental Sealing IP42 Electrostatic Discharge (ESD) DS2208/DS2278 and Cradle: ESD per EN61000-4-2, +/-15 KV Air, +/-8 KV Direct, +/-8 KV Indirect Ambient Light Immunity 0 to 10,000 Foot Candles/0 to 107,600 Lux RADIO SPECIFICATIONS Bluetooth Radio Standard Bluetooth Version 4.0 with BLE: Class 2 33 ft. (10.0m), Serial Port and HID Profiles; output power adjustable down from 2.0 dBm in 8 Steps DECODE CAPABILITIES 3 1D Code 39, Code 128, Code 93, Codabar/NW7, Code 11, MSI Plessey, UPC/EAN, I 2 of 5, Korean 3 of 5, GS1 DataBar, Base 32 (Italian Pharma) 2D PDF417, Composite Codes, TLC-39, Aztec, Data Matrix, MaxiCode, QR Code, Micro QR, Chinese Sensible (Han Xin), Postal Codes</description>
			       <g:price>7500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Zebra DS2208</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/ls2208.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Honeywell Xenon MS 1900 2D Barcode Scanner </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/honeywell-xenon-ms-1900-2d-barcode-scanner.html</link>
			       <description>Honeywell Xenon MS1900 GHD 2D Barcode Scanner Specification Mechanical Dimensions (LxWxH) 104 mm x 71 mm x 160 mm (4.1 x 2.8 x 6.3 )</description>
			       <g:price>17500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Honeywell Xenon</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/Honeywell_Xenon_1900GHD_2D_dreamtechcombd-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Honeywell Voyager MS9520 Barcode Scanner </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/honeywell-voyager-ms9520-barcode-scanner.html</link>
			       <description>Honeywell Voyager MS9520 Best Quality Barcode Scanner Product features Honeywell Voyager MS9540 barcode scanners Automatic trigger use scanner as either a hand-held device or a fixed presentation scanner when mounted in the stand 650-Nanometer laser: high-visibility laser allows user to place laser line on selected bar Code Flash ROM: future proof POS system with free firmware updates via Metroset2 software and standard PC Product description Honeywell Voyager 9500 Series of hand-held, single-line laser scanners offer aggressive scanning of all standard 1D bar codes. The Voyager Series of hand-held, single-line bar Code scanners have United form with function in becoming the industry benchmark for value and performance. These sleek scanners feature patented automatic Infrared activation and Decode all standard 1D bar codes, including GS1 databartm (formerly known as rss codes). voyagercg 9540 also includes patented codegate technology which allows the user to easily target the desired bar Code and complete data transmission with the press of a single button. For presentation scanning, Honeywell offers a stand with automatic in-stand detection technology. * One year Warranty.</description>
			       <g:price>19500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>ms9520</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/Honeywell_1200G_Barcode_Scanner_dreamtechcombd-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Honeywell Voyager 1202G Barcode Scanner </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/honeywell-voyager-1202g-barcode-scanner.html</link>
			       <description>Honeywell Voyager 1202G Bluetooth Wireless Barcode Scanner Description The Honeywell Voyager 1202G Barcode Scanner -bf single-line laser scanner incorporates breakthrough battery-free technology, offering the freedom of Bluetooth wireless technology without the maintenance hassle, long recharge time, or environmental disposal issues associated with traditional batteries. Built on the proven Voyager platform, the 1202g-bf delivers aggressive linear barcode scanning performance””even on poor quality or damaged barcodes. General Information Manufacturer Part Number: 1202G Brand Name: Honeywell Product Line: Voyager Product Model: 1202g</description>
			       <g:price>18500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Voyager 1202G</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/1202g.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Thermal Transfer Label Printer GP-1125Z </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/thermal-transfer-label-printer-gp-1125z.html</link>
			       <description>Famous Brand: Gprinter Thermal Transfer Label Printer GP-1125Z Specification Model: GP-1124Z GP-1125Z Dimontion 210(W)×180(H)×285(L) Weight 2.09KG Power supply Input: AC 110-240V Output: DC 24V 2.5A,60W built-in power adapter Environment Work environment temperature 5~40 (41~104 ) humidity 25~85% Storage temperature-40~60 (-40~140 ) humidity 10~90% Interface Serial+USB+Parallel Serial+USB+Parallel+Ethernet Print specification Model GP-1124Z GP-1125Z Dot density 203dots/inch(8dots/mm) Print method Ribbon/Thermal Dot size(W×L) 0.125×0.125 mm (1 mm = 8 dots) Print speed inch/s 2~5 inch/s Maximum print width 108 mm(4.25") Maximum print length 2286 mm(90") Pulse excitation 1*108 pulse Thermal film(reliability) 50KM</description>
			       <g:price>23000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>5080</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/GP-3120TL_2.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Honeywell Orbit 7190G Barcode Scanner </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/honeywell-orbit-7190g-barcode-scanner.html</link>
			       <description>Honeywell Orbit 7190G Table Barcode Scanner Description The Honeywell Orbit 7190G Barcode Scanner, superior 1D laser scanning performance of Orbit series scanners — but adds an area imager for seamless scanning of digital 1D, 2D and PDF codes in a single, convenient device. To speed retail checkouts, the Orbit 7190g scanner features a unique dual-modes design that is optimized for both the cashier and the customer — enabling seamless product barcode scanning and scanning of digital codes off customer smartphones. Data Sheet (PDF)</description>
			       <g:price>15000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Orbit 7190G</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/Omni-Directional-Multi-line-Desktop-Laser-Bar_2-min.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Honeywell Voyager 1250G Barcode Scanner </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/honeywell-voyager-1250g-barcode-scanner.html</link>
			       <description>Honeywell Voyager 1250G Very faster Barcode Scanner Description Honeywell’s Voyager 1250g single-line laser barcode scanner is simple to set up and provides aggressive reading of linear barcodes. The Honeywell 1250G barcode Scanner is capable of reading barcodes up to 23 inches away, reducing reach-related fatigue and improving employee comfort. For users that require hands-free scanning, an easy-to-assemble stand increases throughput by incorporating automatic in-stand detection. Features optimized laser scanning technology to read poorly printed or damaged barcodes.</description>
			       <g:price>7500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Voyager 1250G</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/Honeywell_Voyager_1250G_Scanner_st_dreamtechcombd-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Honeywell Orbit 7120 Barcode Scanner </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/honeywell-orbit-7120-barcode-scanner.html</link>
			       <description>Honeywell Orbit 7120 Omnidirectional Laser Scanner Description 20 scan line omnidirectional pattern: Provides aggressive scanning as an additional benefit to hand presentation applications Adjustable scan head: Ability to tilt scanner 30 for targeted scanning or larger products Orbit 7120 Omnidirectional Laser Scanner Accessories 46-00525 Power Supply: NA plug, 1.0A @ 5.2VDC, 90-255VAC @ 50-60Hz 45-45619 Stand: wall mount/ desk mount for MS7100 Orbit series</description>
			       <g:price>13500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Orbit 7120</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/demo/shop/products-list/Omni_Directional_Bar_Code_Scanner_C545__wwwdreamtechcombd-min-min.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra Symbol DS9208 Barcode Scanner </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-symbol-ds9208-barcode-scanner.html</link>
			       <description>Zebra Symbol DS9208 Barcode Scanner Description: AFFORDABLE NEXT-GENERATION SCANNING TECHNOLOGY FOR TODAY’S MOBILE WORLD Whether you need a barcode scanner that can be used on paper labels or mobile barcodes on the screen of a mobile phone, with the Zebra DS9208, you’ll be ready. You get the versatility to scan any 1D or 2D barcode — from the printed labels in retail that identify product and pricing at the register to mobile coupons, mobile gift and loyalty cards, boarding passes and even theater tickets.</description>
			       <g:price>13000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>DS9208</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/Motorola_Symbol_DS9208_Hands-Freer__.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>BARCODE READER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>S</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> RONGTA RP-325 80MM Thermal Receipt Printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/rongta-rp-325-80mm-thermal-receipt-printer.html</link>
			       <description>RONGTA RP-325 80MM 3 Inch Thermal Receipt Printer Specifications:</description>
			       <g:price>6500 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>RP-325</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/Rongta_RP-325_full.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>POS PRINTER</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Zebra ZT410 203dpi/300dpi Industrial bar code label </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/product/zebra-zt410-203dpi-300dpi-industrial-bar-code-label.html</link>
			       <description>Zebra zt410 Desktop Direct Thermal/Thermal Transfer Label Printer ZT410 Thermal transfer printer / barcode printer Model GT410 Printing method Thermal transfer printing/ direct thermal / thermal sensitive Printing resolution 203dpi/300dpi/600dpi printing speed: 12IPS(305mm / sec) Printing width: 104mm/sec 4.09" Printing length: 990 mm (39") Standard features:   300m standard ribbon   32 bytes RISC processor   In-built EPL and ZPL programme language   3 kinds interface: serial, USB and parallel   printing method : thermal transfer and direct thermal   Housing shell double enhanced plastic structure   With Open ACCESS tm design, quickly for label media and ribbon loading.   recognized Microsoft and Windows driver programme   Chinese Fontset , GB18030 complex font, simplified Simsun typeface (ZPL), complex font KAI and simplified SUNG (EPL)</description>
			       <g:price>99000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>ZT410</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/images/zebra_410_g.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>Shop</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
				<g:gender>female</g:gender>
				<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
				<g:size>OS</g:size>
				<g:color>white/black</g:color>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Xprinter XP-N160II USB Wired Bluetooth Printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/~oaosknmp/product/xprinter-xp-n160ii-usb-wired-bluetooth-printer.html</link>
			       <description>Xprinter XP-N160II USB Wired Bluetooth Printer- Use Laptop, Desktop and Mobile Description: Printing method Direct thermal line Print width 80mm paper width Point density 576 dots / line, or 512 dots / line Printing speed 160 mm / sec Interface Type: USB port + Bluetooth Paper 79.5 0.5 mm Support for a variety of international languages and scripts Support wall mounted Semi-automatic cutter Cash Drawer Output DC 24V / 1A Weight 1.3 kg Dimensions 184 × 143 × 133 mm (L × W × H) Durable Cutter life 50 km printhead life Printing method Direct thermal line Print width 80mm paper width Point density 576 dots / line, or 512 dots / line Printing speed 160 mm / sec Interface Type: USB port + Bluetooth Paper 79.5 0.5 mm Support for a variety of international languages and scripts Support wall mounted Semi-automatic cutter Cash Drawer Output DC 24V / 1A Weight 1.3 kg Dimensions 184 × 143 × 133 mm (L × W × H) Durable Cutter life 50 km printhead life</description>
			       <g:price>8000.99 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>200</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/~oaosknmp/images/demo/shop/products-list/xprinter.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>POINT OF SALE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Thermal Paper Rolls 57 mm x 25mm (60 Rolls/Case) </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/~oaosknmp/product/thermal-paper-receipt-rolls-57-mm-x-25mm.html</link>
			       <description>Cheap Price Good Quality 57mm pos Thermal Paper Roll : For POS Printer 1. 60 Rolls a Case for one lot, fast delivery 2. if big qtys requirements, Pls. contact us for sea cargo distribution</description>
			       <g:price>18 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Roll box</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/~oaosknmp/images/pos_roll_thermal_1_.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> 57*40 Thermal Receipt Paper Roll </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/~oaosknmp/product/57-40-thermal-receipt-paper-roll.html</link>
			       <description>High Quality Paper 57*40 Thermal Receipt Paper Roll Description: Type: Thermal Receipt Paper Roll</description>
			       <g:price>30 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>P57-40</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/~oaosknmp/images/pos_roll_1.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> Thermal Paper 80x80mm For Pos Printer </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/~oaosknmp/product/thermal-paper-80x80mm.html</link>
			       <description>Thermal Paper 80x80mm 60 Gsm Ppaer For Pos Printer Paper Size: 80*80 mm Thermal Roll Made from the best quality Thermal paper Roll, clear to print. Can work with most 80 mm Thermal Roll in the market. thermal pos printer roll Widely used in taxi bill printing, receipt printing, restaurant and online payment information printing, etc. Note: The thermal printer in the picture is not included. 80*80 mm Thermal Roll and More size for order.</description>
			       <g:price>120 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>80x80mm</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/~oaosknmp/images/POS_BOX.jpg</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>PRINTER ACCESSORIES</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
			<item>
			       <title> 10 inch Touch Screen ECR Cash Register Machine </title>
			       <link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/~oaosknmp/product/10-inch-touch-screen-ecr-cash-register-machine.html</link>
			       <description>Suitable For Restaurant,Cafe,Stores,good management for inventory and billing Description : Power supply:DC12V 4A Monitor:10.1 inch capacitive touch screen Customer Display:10.1 inch(1024*600) screen, Customer Display use: LED 8 digital POS Software:Independent intellectual property rights of software Printer:58 thermal receipt printer (included in pos) Cash drawer size:33.5*36.8*8cm CPU:Freescale IMX6 SD ram/NANDFLASH:512MB/16GB Interface:2* RS232,2* USB,1*LAN,1*Cash drawer port 1. Commodity number: 60000 2. Dept. number: 10000 3. Clerk number: 1000 4. Cashier number: 1000 5. Taste number: 100 6. Discount type: 100 7. Payment type: 100 8. Member number: 20000 9. Table number: 2000 10. Tax number: 10 11. Receipt number: 6000 About pos software: *Use for restaurant or mini market *Free training for lifetime</description>
			       <g:price>24000 USD</g:price>
			       <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			       <g:condition>new</g:condition>
			       <g:id>Touch pos</g:id>
			       <g:image_link>https://dreamtech.com.bd/~oaosknmp/images/CASH_REGISTER_MACHINE_TOUCH.png</g:image_link>
			       
				<g:product_type>POINT OF SALE</g:product_type>
				<g:shipping>
				<g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
				</g:shipping>
			       <g:brand>Dreamtech</g:brand>
			       
				<g:identifier_exists>no</g:identifier_exists>
			</item>
		</channel>
</rss>